You've got to be shitting me.
Oh, shit!
Get out of the way!
- Driving all crazy.
- Damn.
I've got a foot chase on a male.
Maybe 13 years, short, with braids,
in the alleys eastbound from fulton.
This kid has bailed out! Bail out!
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
- Fuck!
- Officer, what are you doing?
- What, you need bifocals or something?
- What?
- 0-9. I'm responding.
- 16, 200 north.
I'm gonna need your name.
I'm very sorry, ma'am, all right?
Give me that.
Them expeditions are hard to handle.
With a Lexus I wouldn't have no problem.
You little motherfucker.
- You know how many cars you hit?
- What?
- Don't even think of bullshitting.
- I don't know what you're talking about.
You know how much
fucking paperwork I got now? Huh?
How many hours of my life you owe me,
you little shit?
Damn, yo! That hurt!
- You think that hurts...?
- No, no!
Ah! Ah!
You're so smart,
- let's see how easy you boost a car now.
- Ah!
Ah! Ahh!
When you walk through the garden
watch your back
well I beg your pardon
walk the straight and narrow track
if you walk with Jesus
he 7! Save your soul
gotta keep the devil down in the hole
he's got fire and the fury
at his command
well, you don't got to worry
hold on to Jesus' hand
we 7! Be safe from Satan
when the thunder rolls
but you gotta keep the devil
down in the hole
Oh yeah, mm
we 7! Be safe from Satan
Gotta keep the devil
down in the hole
keep him in the hole in the hole
keep him in the hole
keep him in the...
Down in the hole
down in the hole
keep him in the hole
keep him in the...
Down in the hole
down in the hole
You imagine, rawls sitting in this chair?
Never happen. In this town? Uh-uh.
Yeah, well, we weren't supposed
to have a white mayor, either.
He already overreached
putting rawls in charge.
- De-fucking-facto.
- Motherfucker ain't even sworn in,
already he's got feelers out.
He called the deputy chief in Pittsburgh,
friend of mine, promised
him pie in the sky.
Shee-it, partner, just show
carcetti and everybody else
that they already got the man for the job.
They ain't got to look no further.
The indispensable man.
It was Royce holding you back, ervin.
Now out from under, you shine.
Clay, he's saying everything
goes through bill rawls.
- Any move I try to make...
- You're still the commissioner, ain't you?
- You give an order, theyjump.
- But carcetti...
He gonna fire you? He just showed you
he don't have balls enough.
You just need
to give carcetti a little something.
Make him start seeing you in a new light.
Like what?
Some police shit. I don't know.
Something that looks good to carcetti,
so he can say it was his idea to keep you.
"Police shit"?
Well, whatever it is y'all
do for a living. Look...
Just take care of your end
and let your friends handle theirs.
- Good morning.
- I just dropped my stuff in my room,
and maintenance and Donnelly are checking
the heat. It must be 80 degrees in there.
- 90-minute classes.
- Excuse me?
This time of year, we
go to 90-minute classes.
Concentrated prep in math
and language arts only.
I don't follow. Why the heat?
It's the only way kids will
sit through 90 minutes of anything.
- Make them drowsy?
- Right.
So it's about the tests.
From now until they're done,
everything's about the tests.
- Damn! I ought to go somewhere warm.
- Plymouth rock!
- Where?
- I saw on animal planet, marlin fishing.
Like, Florida, The Bahamas.
That shit looked sweet.
The water was like this... this color, man.
It ain't gonna be that cold this year.
- How you know?
- Global warming.
So why is it so cold already?
Yo, we just getting old.
Yeah. True that.
Where the fuck you been?
Cityjail for a day and a half
till they recogged me.
Then my grandma got sick,
so I was over there for a while.
- Po-po hit you with a charge?
- Just false statement and shit,
for saying I wasn't who I really was.
Damn, so why they was
asking about you like that?
Mm-mm.
- They try talking to you?
- Yeah, about some murder.
- Which one?
- It don't matter which murder,
because I ain't say shit to them bitches.
Yeah, well, I ain't the one
you need to convince.
Plymouth rock! Plymouth rock!
- Why I got to convince him?
- I'm saying, yo.
Po-po come asking about you, you
out of pocket for a few days.
Yeah. He'll definitely hear about it.
I ain't say nothing to nobody. That's why
they dumped my ass in central booking,
because I ain't say a fucking word
to none of 'em.
Yeah, so go tell him that shit.
Shit, man, if it were
me, I'd go to him first.
Yeah, jump out in front of that.
If they come looking for you,
it looks like you got something to hide.
Definitely.
Ghetto bird special. Two for one.
What you want?
Menu, yo. Give him a menu.
- What's good?
- Fuck if I know.
You ain't supposed to cuss
at the customer, motherfucker.
- Darnell.
- All right.
Let me get... pizza.
Pizza. Anything to drink?
Grape soda.
Quiet, please.
- Is that it?
- Yeah.
Thank you. Say thank you.
Yeah. Thank you.
Menu?
Don't he got to say "thank you," too?
- Darnell.
- Why? He's supposed to give it back.
When you are polite to people,
they treat you better. Have a seat, please.
Now you be the waiter,
and Albert, you be the customer.
What you want to eat?
Some crab cakes and a coke.
Hurry that shit up, too.
Been on the phone nonstop
with fourth Avenue.
They insist every
class teaches to the test.
- Oh, god.
- I thought we were the exception.
That's the point of the project.
- They know that.
- No exceptions.
90-minute blocks of math
or language arts only.
They can't do 30 minutes
without climbing the walls.
Isn't there somebody
we can talk with, face to face?
Actually, the area superintendent
wants to see the two of you tomorrow,
nine o'clock in the conference room.
Let's not panic... yet.
¢qué es esto?
- Business as usual.
- Marlo.
- You no know him when we robbed the gang?
- We ain't never been introduced.
Boy's merely a name to me.
If you knew it was marlo,
you'd still go through with it, no?
I wish I'd have known.
I'd have enjoyed it that much more.
Bubs. It's herc.
You hungry?
Yo, what you done was fucked up, man.
- I felt bad when I heard.
- Not only were you late,
you just rolled right past.
Ain't you see me getting beat?
- We rolled by?
- I seen you with the blue light on, man.
Whatever. Look, we had
a communication problem, I admit.
But I'm gonna get you a phone today.
That's gonna solve it for us. You'll see.
Thing is, there's this camera,
police department video camera,
disappeared a few weeks back.
For various reasons that I can't get into,
I got to get it back somehow.
Camera?
Yeah. This fella marlo probably took it.
I don't know if he hocked it...
You bothering me about a camera?
You supposed to have my back, remember?
- Five minutes, you told me.
- I know. I owe on the deal.
It's Tyrone's, chicken wings.
Here's the thing. I want
you to put it out there
that there's a $500 bounty on this camera
if it comes back.
- No questions asked.
- 500?
Swear to god. I'm good for it.
If it's the right camera.
Here's the model and serial number.
500 for the camera
and chicken for bubs, huh?
Another 100 to you if this happens. But
I need this camera quick or shit will fly.
Look, man, it's not about
the money for me right now.
This motherfucker,
he messing with my livelihood here.
They're always coming back, always.
- He's like some Terminator and shit.
- I'm with you.
I'll do all I can to help you with your
problem, and you're gonna help me out with mine.
Who the fuck is Randy?
A little hopper from around the way.
He ain't in the game but he with Michael.
He talking to police?
I know it. He was the one I told,
"go tell Lex to go up to the alley.
- "Patrice is waiting."
- You were supposed to do that.
I know, but this way,
try to keep some distance
between me and Lex, right?
You tell this Randy what happened to Lex?
No, I swear it.
Go, motherfucker.
The fuck you still waiting for?
- What the fuck y'all following me for?
- Easy, son.
Naw, ain't nobody walking with me nowhere.
- What's up with this Randy?
- He can't hurt us.
- He a snitch, though.
- Put that around, then.
- Slim.
- Marlo.
- How you feeling?
- Can't complain, yo.
Getting to be that time, though.
Joe wanted me to check in, you know.
All right. Pull up a
chair. Let's chop it up.
- Now, that there a barksdale boy.
- So?
Don't add up.
Interesting, though.
Got a burner, see?
If anything else comes up, you call me.
If this guy robs you again, make
sure he's holding. The more the better.
Shit, I ain't got money for all that.
There's 40 minutes on that,
and my number's in there.
I'm gonna call you today or tomorrow
at the latest.
One and one.
Damn, son. He did a number on you.
- Who was it?
- Officer Walker.
Walker be evil.
- What up?
- Four.
- We ought to fuck him up.
- Walker? Yo, he the police.
I'm just saying.
He said next time I steal a car,
I'm finding myself dead.
- You gonna do as he say?
- Fuck, no.
Soon as I get this shit off,
I'll be running his ass all over town.
Yo, shit!
Told you, namond.
Gave you fair warning, didn't I?
- I ain't done nothing.
- Get the cash. Got you cold.
Hair like that, I saw
you from east Baltimore.
- Get the fuck off of me, man.
- Shut up!
- Look what I found.
- That ain't fucking mine!
Hands on the car! Spread legs.
- I ain't fucking got...
- Shut up!
How you like it so far? Having fun?
Guess what? Gets better.
Give me your hands.
Watch your head.
Damn. Y'all not wasting any time, huh?
Nerese let us stage in the council suite
till the inauguration.
No doubt, after your
showing in the general.
- No doubt.
- 81%?
82. In a city where democrats
outnumber Republicans nine to one...
Anything less would have
been an embarrassment.
What can we do for you, senator?
Well, uh, first of all, I
wanted to clear the air.
No hard feelings
over what happened during the primary...
You gonna give the money back?
- Senator, it's been a very long day.
- I'll cut to the chase.
I understand you have a problem
at the top of the police department.
You asked burrell to resign. He declined.
- I'm looking for a replacement.
- The ministers like burrell.
So does the council president.
We're confident that when
we identify a suitable candidate,
Ms. Campbell and the ministers
will see the wisdom of new leadership.
Except y'all need to get
a pay raise through the city council.
Pay raise would help.
I can ask nerese about
that pay raise getting passed,
maybe convince some ministers
they need to move on from burrell.
The situation would have to be resolved
sooner rather than later.
Do my best, partner.
And what do we do for you in return?
I'm in Annapolis.
Word I'm hearing, you may be there too,
in a couple of years.
We may find ourselves
working together closely.
Thanks for your time.
Jesus Christ.
He's slick.
Apologizes for the short con and in the
next breath, setting us up for the long.
- He and burrell are as thick as thieves.
- What is the long con?
At least we know he's running one.
- Try calling again.
- Man, I know she not gonna answer.
My moms don't answer when she go to ac.
- When she coming back?
- She going to New York after.
- What's she doing in New York?
- Shopping.
Going to see some show, the color purple.
See, now this is where my job gets good.
You reach a guardian, the juvenile master's
gonna recog you on a first-time drug offense.
But now you'd better have
a toothbrush on you, son,
because it's gonna be baby booking tonight.
Namond, you scared?
If it was cheltenham, I don't blame you,
but baby booking's just across town.
The east side be beefing
with the West Side in there.
There's dudes be getting raped and shit.
I mean, that's what I be hearing.
It's bad in there. I don't
know if it's... that bad.
Well, I hear different.
You got no other family?
I got a aunt down in pg county.
You got a number?
- Well, I ain't driving you this late...
- Come on, man.
Tell you what.
Two of my guys are working a double,
working midnight shift tonight.
If you can plant yourself on that bench
there, you can stay here for the night.
But first thing tomorrow,
you raise that aunt or raise your moms,
or I got to process you.
You don't move off that bench.
You need the bathroom, you go now.
Otherwise... sit tight
and don't give anybody any trouble,
- or they'll process you right then and there.
- I'm cool. Thanks.
Fucking charity ward here.
I'll go tell the shift commander.
Yo, lieutenant...
- He a 50?
- No.
Probably copping it for my moms.
That's why?
Look. I told y'all, I just want him gone.
I just want him away from me and bug.
What the fuck did he do to you?
All right.
We'll take care of it, boss.
- Another church burglary last night.
- Madison park methodist.
This would be what you'd call a rash.
We could use some ointment.
We need to arrest these fucks.
- We getting anywhere on that?
- Not yet.
- Who caught the last one? Mcnulty?
- Working it. We should talk.
- All right.
- Word from on high is to sweep corners.
- They want arrests to double.
- How the fuck how?
- The election's over.
- Quality-of-life violations.
- What are we talking about, loitering?
- Disorderly, public indecency.
- This is horseshit.
- Broken-windows theory.
- Worked in New York.
- This ain't New York.
- But it could work here.
- Never has.
- Never been done right.
- Open containers, too.
- No writing tickets?
- We'll do more of that too.
But the commissioner himself
wants to juke arrests.
- Open container used to be sacrosanct.
- In a paper bag.
They gave you that much respect.
A man's beverage was his business.
- You took them to a restaurant?
- Yeah. Ruth Chris.
- Linen napkins.
- Yeah. Silverware, more than one fork.
_ how'd they do?
_ pretty well, considering.
- Did they embarrass us?
- Us?
No, we're fine with it, but...
I mean, they were intimidated,
embarrassed and awkward as hell,
but they made it through.
These aren't the kids that can sit still
for the statewide tests,
much less do well on them.
These were the kids that made it
impossible for anyone to do well.
So, we're writing them off?
No, that's what we're not doing.
- You're not educating, you're socializing.
- They weren't being educated before.
- Excuse me?
- Hold on. What he's saying is this.
You put a textbook in front of these kids,
or teach them every problem on some
statewide test, it won't matter, none of it,
because they're not learning for our world
they're learning for theirs.
They know what they're training for
and what everyone expects them to be.
I expect them to be students.
But it's not about you or us,
or the tests or the system.
It's what they expect of themselves.
Every single one of them
is headed back to the corners.
Their brothers and
sisters, shit, their parents,
they came through these same classrooms.
We pretended to teach,
they pretended to learn.
Where'd they end up?
The same damn corners.
I mean, they're not fools, these kids.
They don't know our world,
but they know their own.
I mean, Jesus, they...
They see right through us.
We made that clear
when you approved the project.
Provisionally approved.
And then, we made it clear
that we would be addressing children
that required socialization
before they could be properly educated.
We can't lie.
Not to them.
Captain, line three.
Roll call's over.
You get a line on your mother yet?
Fucking neglect case here, I want it.
How about that aunt?
Ain't nobody else?
No other responsible adult?
- Like who?
- I don't know.
I'm giving you one last shot,
cos once I go on the street
you're gonna have to go to booking.
I got a teacher.
Mr. Colvin. You know him?
He used to be police.
Tall? Bald?
Yeah.
Yeah, I know him.
What if you get the one snitch?
The one with the cart. What's his name?
Bubbles.
Bubbles. Yeah.
You get bubbles to say he's fuzzy dunlop.
Bubbles has been a registered ci for years.
Kima gave him a number
back when she was in plain clothes.
Herc, you worked with him
under that number on the barksdale stuff.
- So how would you fuck up the ID?
- Fuck me, man.
Look. The only way to
get out from under this
is to stop fucking lying, ok?
Grab your dick, walk into marimow's office,
and say, "lieutenant, I made a mistake.
"I attributed my PC to an informant
when in fact I had it off a camera."
That I got from isd without going
through the proper channels. No.
He's gonna take my stripes.
Maybe he does. But if you wait
until isd asks for that camera
and he figures out the lie,
he takes your fucking balls.
Come on! Let's go!
Just around the corner.
Got you now, motherfucker.
In going over my paperwork,
it occurs to me I may have been neglectful.
Look at all this crap!
Every day, more and more of Lester
freamon's bullshit washes up with us.
- What the fuck are you saying?
- My paperwork may have been a little sloppy,
and as a result,
I confused myself on some things.
No shit, you were sloppy.
I went back a couple weeks
on your run sheets.
Nothing there references
a meet with a ci 238.
- You went through my run sheets?
- The best I could.
- Sir, listen...
- I don't care. Turn that fucking thing off.
I am starting to believe
that this fuzzy fella doesn't exist.
I am starting to believe that you just
followed Stanfield into the train station
and grabbed the first broad
he brushed up against.
- That what happened?
- No. No, sir.
You lie to me now, sergeant, and I
guaran-fucking-tee you I will jam you up,
ship this whole mess to iid
and pass out sandwiches at your execution.
Yes, sir.
You haven't had a case yet worth talking
about, not on marlo Stanfield, not on anyone.
You bring me something
other than iid complaints,
and I might have reason
to let a few things slide.
Mad at me?
- Come on, now.
- Dukie's just mad at everybody.
Snitch bitch.
Yo, what the fuck was that?
I don't know.
I can't believe y'all doing this shit.
You're degrading the quality of life
in this neighborhood.
- Malt liquor.
- Come on, man!
Brother, shake hands with a pilsner,
maybe a nice pale ale.
Hell, what...? Man! My brew! My shoes!
- God! Man.
- What's the violation?
Parking in a bus stop,
expired registration.
- First-class police work.
- This is the word from up on high,
straight from the eighth floor downtown.
Blessed bosses juking stats
for the new administration.
I know you think it's bullshit
but I spend my shift where they tell me.
Baker, let me tell you a little secret.
A patrolling officer on his beat
is the one true dictatorship in america.
We can lock a guy up on a humble,
lock him up for real,
or we can say, fuck it, pull under the
expressway and drink ourselves to death,
and our partners will cover it.
So no one, and I mean no one,
tells us how to waste our shift.
Pulled the reports on
those church burglaries.
- Yeah?
- Yeah. There's a pattern.
Times and locations.
They're working west by northwest
through sandtown-Winchester.
The last three, here, here, and here,
these ones in blue
are the churches they haven't hit.
- This is from the incident reports?
- That's why we do the paperwork.
Giving me a fucking ticket, man?
Are you out of your motherfucking mind?
- I live here, man!
- This could get out of hand.
- That's what we want, isn't it? More arrests?
- Why you messin' with me, man?
Nojustice, no peace.
It'll only be for tonight.
Mama gets back from New York tomorrow.
Your call.
The young man seems
to think highly of you, boss.
He invoked your name
with a measure of respect.
It wasn't but a few weeks ago I was with him
being called everything but a child of god.
"Mr. Colvin, sir.
"Fuck you."
Well, at least I said, "mr".
- So what was the charge?
- Slinging.
He'd been out there a few weeks or so.
First pop, second warning from me.
Maybe you should put him
on the juvenile bus.
He want so bad to be a gangster, maybe
it's time he get a taste of a real lockup?
Come on, Mr. C, don't do me like that.
I made him sleep on the deu bench
last night, if that counts for anything.
Isn't there anybody else?
Friend, relative, anybody?
You've always been good
with the knuckleheads, boss.
All right. Let me go call my wife.
Yeah. Go up in that building.
- Mm, man, that was delicious.
- There's more.
No, ma'am. Saving room for the cobbler.
- Ala mode?
- Uh huh?
Would you like ice cream on it?
- Oh, yes, ma'am.
- Nice manners.
From what you told me on the phone, bunny,
I was expecting more of an adventure.
Bunny?
Only my friends call me bunny.
- Yeah, but why?
- You don't need to know.
And if you tell anybody,
I'll cut your balls off.
I'll cut them off, give 'em to
Donnelly in a jar. Don't doubt me, boy.
You ain't got no kids?
Grown. They at college and past that.
You told me these kids were rough.
Thank you, sweetie. But don't be fooled.
This is his Eddie haskell act.
Eddie haskell? Who that?
You are, son. Trust me.
Take a seat.
Against the wall with the others.
Welcome wagon's coming.
- We need the key to the interview room.
- Why?
- Felony burglary.
- Felony?
Caught them coming out of
St. Martin's on fulton.
Charging them with the one,
but we might work back on a few more.
No shit? Knew there was still
some real criminals left in Baltimore.
Swear to god, I'm seeing citations
forjaywalking.
We're locking people up for open container,
for disorderly, for loitering.
Neighborhood people appreciate
quality-of-life arrests.
We're locking up neighborhood people.
My guys, all they see are stats.
The election's fucking over, right?
Who are we doing this for?
- Is this from burrell or rawls?
- From the chief of patrol.
- It's rolling downhill, for sure.
- Morale?
Split down the middle. The
officers that love the stats are jazzed.
- The rest of you?
- We don't know where to turn.
I thought a new mayor might
change this shit, not ramp it up.
You still fucking that bitch?
Yeah. It burning like hell, man.
When you gonna burn the bitch back?
Check it.
Slim!
- B, what up?
- All right.
- Poot.
- It's good.
- Heard you out.
- Yeah.
- Welcome home.
- Thanks, dawg.
And you with prop Joe now.
- Never would have thought.
- Yeah, well, life's strange.
Yeah. Holler.
Bodie... how you and Mario?
You ok with him?
As far as I know, yeah. Why?
- What he did to your boy.
- What boy are you talking?
Big boy, the one rub his hands together
all the time?
Kevin? What about him?
You ain't heard?
Chris and snoop walked him down an alley.
He in a vacant now.
How you know that?
I seen them lay hands on the boy.
And now the word out on the street.
Sorry, dawg.
Let's roll.
Plymouth rock.
Got that Plymouth rock.
All right.
But now look at the next
example question on page 20.
As you can see... if you turn to page 20,
they will sometimes ask you
for words that are
the opposite of words that are underlined.
- Thank you, Mr. Pryzbylewski.
- Thank you.
All right, put away your test notebooks.
Work on those tomorrow.
We have 45 minutes.
We can do last of the mohicans...
Or practise probabilities.
Yeah.
- I'll get the stuff, Mr. Prezbo.
- All right.
I want to see everybody's worksheets out.
Kareem, you want to play dice with me?
Not with you.
And we're not just playing games here,
- we're doing math.
- I'll roll with you, man. Come on.
No kidding. We are.
That's my boy resting his head, see?
Hey, renaldo, you want one?
- No.
- They're from faidley's, yo.
He might stay home all day, you know?
We gonna find out, ain't we?
- It's about my dss code.
- You have an appointment?
- Why I need an appointment?
- She doesn't need an appointment.
- Just making it realistic.
- So I get to see somebody?
- Take a number and wait.
- I need to see somebody now.
Don't get angry. Anger doesn't help.
It makes people defensive.
Tell her what you need calmly.
- Card didn't come this month.
- We mailed it.
- Maybe it got stolen.
- Sorry. Nothing we can do.
- Fuck you.
- Chandra!
- She ain't helping me.
- That's how they do.
- Just tell her what you need.
- Need another card, bitch.
- Chandra!
- And that's real too.
Fuck you for real.
Ooh!
Calm down, calm down. Go with Ms. Mason.
- Get your hands off!
- Ms. Mason!
- I'll get the school police.
- You all right?
She was like...
- And then... she was like...
- Typical day?
I wouldn't know. My first time.
Your first time?
Mrs. Donnelly oversees this project.
Good morning, ladies.
Help a man get something to eat?
God bless.
Good morning, reverend.
Yo.
- Glad you finally answered.
- I was in a meeting.
You got the asshole pinned down?
Nah, I got marlo's people,
getting ready to make a drop.
- Where?
- Emerson, near pulaski.
- You eyeballing them now?
- Yeah, he got the package.
Black bag, putting it in the trunk.
- He getting in now.
- What make?
Late model Lincoln. You want the license?
- Yeah, give it.
- P-r-8-z-g-o-d.
Yeah, he pulling out now,
turning down gilmore.
Dozerman, get me foxtrot.
Good job, bubs. We're on it.
Ladies, a cellphone?
It's got, like, a half hour on it.
No, thank you.
What I saw today wasn't education
as I understand the term,
and they didn't seem
very socialized, either.
- You didn't catch us on our best day.
- Or your worst day?
On the whole, they've
made a lot of progress.
Look, they come to class.
They're more engaged. We're reaching them.
- Fewer outbursts, no suspensions.
- But are they learning anything?
- Yes. We believe they are.
- Be truthful.
If this program were to continue
through the rest of the school year,
how many of your students could realistically
be expected to return to a regular classroom?
What do you think, Ms. Duquette?
Namond, Darnell, maybe zenobia.
Considering where we started, and that
those kids ain't tearing up other classes...
Ok. Mrs. Donnelly.
A tremendous achievement.
Mr. Withers?
I'll go along with Mrs. Donnelly.
You haven't said anything yet.
I just don't see it.
Many of these kids are profoundly damaged.
What they've seen, how they've lived.
And I think any gain or
progress is temporary.
I think this project may be flawed.
Foxtrot 23-30.
We have a visual on the suspect.
Vehicle headed east on mulberry.
Do you copy?
- 10-4. We're almost there.
- 10-4.
After your phone call, I checked.
It came directly from burrell.
He bypassed rawls after I told him...
Burrell's making a
play for you to keep him.
By... just... what did you call that?
- Juking the stats.
- Guy is unbelievable.
It runs completely counter
to all my discussions with rawls,
with you, with everyone.
He's also serving notice.
He's reasserting control of the department.
He probably figures if you can't fire him,
then you can't fire him.
- Does rawls know?
- My guess is rawls heard days ago
from half a dozen district commanders.
- Why not come to me?
- Talk to him.
Why did you come to me?
Why not go to rawls?
Because I need to know if you're serious.
If rawls came to you
and this shit is still going on,
then you're ok with it,
which is for me a problem.
If he didn't come to you, then either
he's ok with it, which is also a problem,
or he's letting it go
trying to give burrell enough rope
for you to get angry
and fire him for insubordination.
But I need to know where you stand.
I gave you my word.
Yes. You did.
Well, thanks for going outside
the chain of command.
Don't expect me to make a habit of it.
Stay in the car. Stay in the car.
Keep your hands on the wheel.
- Let's see those hands.
- What's the problem, officer?
Step slowly out of the vehicle.
Keep your hands up.
Unh! Son, be gentler than that.
Shut the fuck up. I ain't your son.
This guy...
What's this, huh? What's this?
Know what? I'm gonna damn sure
get your name and badge number.
Daniels. I don't think I know him.
He hasn't played much politics,
though he used to be married to
the new councilwoman in the 11th.
- Marla Daniels?
- Mm. That's the one.
This is the last man we want
as police commissioner, nerese.
I mean, I squared off against this fella
a few years back,
and he wouldn't listen to me.
He won't listen to you, the ministers
or anyone in the community.
- Just carcetti?
- Mm-hm.
He's the mayor's boy, definitely.
- Carcetti wants how much of a salary bump?
- 50,000, at least,
- to be competitive nationally.
- Give him 25.
Enough to make him think
he can win you over eventually
but less than he needs
to entice anyone real.
Meanwhile, carcetti's gonna have
to give Daniels six months in cid
before he can bump him again,
for appearances' sake.
So we're buying time here.
Enough for ervin to show
the mayor who butters the bread.
And for events to take
the new-penny shine off Cedric Daniels.
I happen to know he's less
the Saint than he pretends to be.
This is, uh, senator Davis.
Is the mayor in at the moment?
Well... you just tell him his friend Clay
got the council president to UN-ass
a salary bump for the police commissioner.
You tell him...
Write this down, now.
You tell him that senator Davis
has his interests at heart.
Right. Thanks.
Hey, ma. How was New York?
Hey, Ms. Brice. How are you?
Who asking?
This is my teacher, mom, Mr. Colvin.
Why he here? You in trouble?
He stayed at our house last night,
you being in New York and all.
Tell her.
The cops picked me
up, saying I was slinging.
They was gonna send me to baby booking.
But we took him in.
You leave my son the fuck alone.
And you, you afraid to go to baby booking?
The fuck is wrong with you, boy?
Get in the damn house!
Kid got the point.
All these drunk and disorderlies,
graffiti artists, and public urinators,
and we come in with
a pair of felony burglaries.
Nice of you to give him the collar.
He might turn out a decent police.
Gotta come from somewhere.
Young generation.
What about you guys?
Gonna follow in your dad's footsteps?
Hello, I don't think so.
- Not.
- What, then?
- Video game designer.
- Rock star.
- Ahh.
- They want to make money.
- You schooled them well.
- How about you, little bunk?
You gonna be a detective, like your daddy?
- Chief of police.
- Nah.
Why not? How about you?
He's still in that, you know,
pediatric neurosurgeon stage.
- Hey.
- Elena, how are you doing?
- I'm good. How are you?
- Can't complain.
- Hey, boys. How are you?
Can you say "hi"?
Listen. They're fine.
They really do have manners.
- It's all right. My kids are the same way.
- We're just finishing up. Sit down.
Uh... ok. Just for a minute.
Dad, five bucks for the jukebox?
What? What happened
to three plays for a quarter?
- Um... homework?
- Done, dad helped us.
I got off early. Here.
You want to go, too?
- So what are you drinking?
- I'll have a white wine.
I'm good, thanks.
So it's true? You quit drinking?
Well, I have a beer now and again.
No big deal.
How's Dennis?
Dennis is... Dennis.
We're close, we're not.
You know, we'll see.
- How's beadie?
- We're good.
- The kids have my number, but...
- Hm.
Wow.
If I had known you were gonna
grow up to be a grown-up...
Pssh, man.
And I'm the one told him to do the
right thing and go talk to the man.
Don't seem that way now, do it?
Yo, you got to look at
it from marlo's point of view.
- How is it different from Wallace?
- Stringer said Wallace snitched.
- Yo, Kevin might have snitched too.
- Man, but he didn't.
- And we had to do Wallace!
- Yo, marlo thought he had to do Kevin.
- Man.
- But he didn't.
That's what I'm saying.
- It's cold, motherfucker.
- It's a cold world, bodie.
Thought you said it was getting warmer.
World going one way, people another, yo.
Now, Elton brand, what you know about him?
Nothing. You see?
Bug, you seen your daddy?
Went to the store.
- Where you going?
- I'm gonna go look for him.
- You ain't gonna find him.
- Why not?
Because he ain't coming back.
Thanks.
- What's this about?
- Like you don't know.
Man, I ain't been home long enough
to get in somebody's shit.
You like boys, motherfucker?
- What?
- Boys. You like fucking them?
Man, I like pussy. All right? Booty.
Living with a woman now.
She got kids?
I ain't touch them kids! Who told you that?
I know what you're saying, but when
you're in the inside, ain't no pussy.
Well, yeah, shit. You've been inside.
Man got to bust his nut,
you know what I'm sayin'?
I do.
Damn. You didn't even wait
to get the motherfucker in the house.