See, to cap a motherfucker,
you put a pistol to his head,
say, "pow," and he tagged.
- But when Chris and them do it--
- Yo, it ain't working, Na'.
- I know you making this up.
- Word to my mother, yo. Lex ain't dead.
I seen him creeping in an alley
last night near the playground.
Everybody know Lex is dead.
Nah, there's dead,
and there's special dead.
Yeah, Chris working
that juju shit.
Nah, man, what I'm saying
is they zombies.
Why you think he take them into vacants?
He need time to change them.
You don't believe me,
yo, it's on you.
Yo, they funnin',
ain't they, Michael?
I don't know about
that voodoo shit, man, but Chris
is definitely doing something--
get a nigger to walk up in there
knowing he about
to get capped, man.
Chris, he different. You can tell
by them coon-ass country clothes
that nigger be wearing.
Nine?
Nah, too much bark.
Probably a.40-cal.
Yeah, man,
this is serious business.
So you saying
Lex is a zombie?
Pookie, Byron,
all them niggers.
- And Chris?
- Yeah, Chris-- Zombie Master.
I knew this
wasn't going away.
That's what we've been trying
to tell you, yo. Chris got the power.
He tell them to come,
and they gotta come--
Iike the devil do
with the damned.
What you think
Chris got them doing?
They're probably
spies, man.
Can't figure any other way
Marlo knows so much.
Yeah, that's what it is. Like in this
movie, "Zombie Killer" or something.
They came out at night, hunting.
- Hunting?
- Yeah, man. They--
Yeah, and in that movie they was
snatching people up,
stealing their warmth.
St. Jude, patron
of lost causes.
Tell me you ain't
been on bended knee
whispering in his saintly ear
each and every night
before you close
those peepers.
I know you have, Tommy,
catch a break like this.
Assigned a rookie--
a broad, no less--
as lead detective.
Pulled a good man off,
too, I heard.
Hmm. Tom.
Tommy, remember--
anything you need.
He's a piece of work.
Valchek?
Comes with the territory.
You want the First District
council seat,
you make nice with whatever Polish
or Greek commander
- they dump in the southeast.
- Not ltalian.
No, there ain't enough of us left
down there.
- You think he has this right?
- That Royce tampered with the case?
No way the mayor knows.
You're right. This one has Ervin Burrell
written all over it.
Fuck if the mayor knows or not.
If it's true,
we get it out there quick
and bang him hard.
- I go public?
- They can't spin this.
They sabotaged
a criminal case.
No spin on a knuckleball, you still
can't tell how it's gonna break.
We feed it to Tony Gray. We keep
ourselves out of the line of fire,
sting Royce,
and as an added bonus,
give Gray's campaign
a boost
which comes at the expense
of the mayor's base.
I'm a devious motherfucker
once I get going.
So all told,
we're looking at 13 warrants
and six locations.
And given my staffing
situation...
Not a problem.
I can give you my D.E.U.,
Flex, and Ops squads.
- A sector of uniforms if you need it.
- Great.
The problem is, you're wasting a wiretap
on street-level arrests.
We do these raids right,
we might catch Marlo
or one of his lieutenants
at one of these locations,
- get them with dope on the table.
- Marlo Stanfield--
in a room,
with dope on the table?
I've kicked down doors
and surprised bigger players than him.
Well, let me warn you,
Lieutenant--
I am not about
to litigate a wiretap
for a handful
of street rips.
Well... that's on you,
Counselor.
No, it's not.
Major, see you tomorrow.
Floaters--
you had any more?
- No more than usual for the season.
- What about decomps?
What do you got
in the decomp room?
- Two or three unidentifieds.
- Found in Baltimore?
No. Actually,
two from Prince George's,
- one from Dorchester.
- Nah, he wouldn't drive that far.
Let me get
this straight:
You're looking for extra bodies,
no one in particular,
other than this one kid you already
put out on the teletype.
Yeah. You on it.
You fellas
don't have enough work?
If you do your classwork,
homework,
you earn stickers.
Dag, yo, every day
you be changing it up.
You got us confused, Mr. P.
Behave in class,
that's another sticker.
At the end of the week, the four
with the most stickers get a prize
and are eligible for a grand drawing
at the end of the month.
Don't do your work,
misbehave in class...
...your name goes here.
Detention-- a full hour after school,
no exceptions.
So it's up to you--
stickers for prizes
or stay with me
after school.
Yo, Mr. P., why you do me
detention, huh?
You interrupted
the class, Namond.
Yo, when you first came in here,
you was all treating us straight up,
and now you just dog me
before I even know the rules.
That ain't right, man.
When you're right, Namond,
you're right.
Hey, Mr. P., I want me
some of them stickers.
Zenobia,
you have to do your work.
I want to,
but I ain't got no pencils.
I don't want
no damn welfare pencil!
It seems to me
there are two kinds of kids
walking in this building--
stoop kids
and corner kids.
- Excuse me?
- You know, stoop kids
stay on their front steps
when their parents tell them.
The others go down
to the corners.
They can't sit still in the class.
The others can and do.
- So separate the two.
- That's tracking.
- Excuse me?
- Tracking students.
It's a nasty phrase
in educational circles.
It refers to the grouping of children
based on expected performance.
- What's wrong with it?
- It says you have reduced expectations
for certain students, that you expect
less from them academically.
So you pretend
to teach all these kids,
and the truth is,
you ain't teaching any of them.
But what if
the stoop kids
could be in classrooms
where there was no disruptions?
- And the corner kids?
- They're the ones you're after, right?
That's why you got
the grant money.
As long as this doesn't involve
warehousing children,
I'm for anything that
allows me to do my job.
Every teacher here
will tell you the same.
The trick for you is
to come up with a program
that actually addresses itself
to the corner kids.
We start pulling kids out of regular
classes-- won't they be stigmatized?
There's not a stigma in being
booted out of class every other day?
Question is,
how do we identify
the corner kids?
That won't be a problem.
Okay. Okay.
You understand the work?
Come on, this is easy.
I know you can do it.
You're not giving me a choice.
You have detention.
Yo, Na', Mrs. D.
shaking bushes.
Back to your seats.
What the fuck?
She got my blade, yo.
I said,
"Back to your seats."
Yo, Mrs. D. be stealing shit.
I ain't never gonna
get my blade back.
Yo, what are you all up on me for?
I do my work.
I'm not your yo.
Show me your work.
Yeah, I see.
Yo, my hand hurting from all this
learning. You got some Tylenol?
What I got for you
is detention.
Oh-hh!
- You know what? Fuck you, Prezbo.
- Oh-hh!
Fucking gimpy-assed,
big-grill motherfucker.
That's it.
You're out of here!
Go!
Get your police stick
out your desk and beat me.
- You know you fucking want to.
- Oh-hh.
Everyone, back in your seat.
The fuck you
looking at, bitch?
Oh-hh, Ms. Sampson, l--
Namond Brice, if you weren't headed
to the main office,
- you are now.
- Yeah, I was just--
One of the corner
kids, huh?
Yeah, they do step up
when you need them, don't they?
Look, what? You want me to say
you right? You right.
I should have had protection
at the card game.
Done is done.
Now we need to decide what we're
gonna do about Omar.
You make the price right,
somebody gonna get a whiff of that
bushwhacker's ass.
Now you take it
from there.
You think so?
I ain't saying Omar can't be got.
Any nigger can be got.
But once we put
word to ear
and he learn that
we pricing out his head,
he's gonna be trying us
like we're trying him.
- You saying I should let it slide?
- Nah.
Nah, we get at him
another way,
get at him without no bounties,
no bullshit like that.
Barksdale turned this town upside down
hunting him,
and all he ended up looking
was weak.
I ain't no Barksdale.
I'm just saying
talk is cheap.
We sit on it, we gonna figure out a way
to get that faggot.
But till then we don't
say a mumbling word.
I got me six now, and I'll give you
the four later, all right? Come on!
- Nah. I'm gonna need the whole 10 now.
- Sherrod!
- You ain't in school?
- I'm half a day-- teachers' meeting.
Come on, I told you about
those lame excuses, man.
- I was talking to him first.
- Ain't no need for physical contact--
You got $4 for me?
I'm short $4.
What the fuck
are you talking--
Got a cart full of shit, nigger.
What you got for me?
I know you holding.
Where's it at?
You ain't hear?
Okay.
It's in my shoe--
my shoe.
Don't need
the four now, son.
Damn, yo, where the shovel at?
Bury that nigger, man.
Here you go, sir,
thank you.
- Tommy Carcetti, running for mayor.
- Good luck, Tommy.
- Hey, Mr. Carcetti, you got my vote.
- Thanks.
- Tom Carcetti.
- Hey, thank you very much.
- Here you go.
- Good luck, Councilman.
How you doing?
Tommy Carcetti, running for mayor.
Okay, Councilman,
time to hit the West Side.
Pretty motherfucker--
he's gonna make me go
to my game face.
Okay, I'll take 25 of the honeysuckle
incense cones--
they'll keep me
healthy for next week.
- Tommy!
- Excuse me.
Tony Gray's people say
20 minutes at their place.
Shit, Clarence.
Look like you did in '98
when you surprised
the hell out of everyone.
Just bring 'em on.
Why give it to us? Why don't you
stick it to Royce yourself?
Because after what Tommy did
at the debate,
it'll seem like more of the same
if it comes from him.
And if we use it to take four
or five points out of Royce's base,
it helps him as much as us.
Once bitten, twice shy.
With Tommy Carcetti,
I got to always think a step ahead.
Look, Tony, you ain't gonna win.
So the only question is
whether you wanna lose
with 24% of the vote
or 28%.
You bring the numbers up,
you look good
for the legislature--
maybe a congressional run.
- Albert Stokes.
- Here.
Mr. P., can I go? My moms told me to go
straight home after school.
Mine too.
You should have thought of that
before you smeared ink
all over my desk.
Weren't my fault.
My pen exploded.
Michael.
Michael Lee?
Mr. P., please,
can I go?
I ain't eat no lunch, and my stomach
making all these noises.
Look, I won't ever disrespect
your pencil again, I promise.
Zenobia, it wasn't
about the pencil.
Please, Mr. P.
- Okay okay, all right.
- All right.
Just this one time,
I'll make an exception.
But next time, expect
to stay the full hour.
- Why are you here?
- Came to say sorry.
I didn't mean to get
all up in your face like that.
I appreciate that, Namond.
It takes courage
to admit when you're wrong.
What I can't understand-- I've seen you
in Ms. Sampson's class doing your work.
- Why can't you do the same in here?
- I mean to, I do.
It's just the evil get in me and before
I know it, I go off.
Well...
tomorrow we'll see
if we can do better.
Can't tomorrow.
Mrs. D. put me out.
I gotta bump.
Later, Mr. P.
If you can wait
outside...
It's okay.
He can stay.
Thank you.
Mr. P., you know
Michael can't make it to detention.
I know he didn't.
Now it's doubled.
- He's got two days to serve.
- Nah, I mean, he can't.
He got to go pick up
his little brother from school.
Well, he'll just have to
find somebody else to do that.
It-- it ain't like that.
I mean, Michael would come
if he could,
but wouldn't have nobody else
to pick up his little brother Bug.
You know, his mother,
she on that stuff.
We walking home.
You coming?
Oh, no, I'm waiting on Alpo.
Ms. Sampson got him doing detention.
- You gonna be here till, like, 5:00.
- Yeah, she a hard lady.
She don't ever give
a brother no play.
- All right. I'll holla at you later.
- All right, yo.
So you're not gonna be
in the NBA?
Then it must be the NFL?
I thought all the boys in class
were gonna join the pros.
Nah, that's just
something we say.
So what about you?
What do you wanna be
when you grow up?
I'm gonna own
my own store.
That's smart. You're gonna need
to know a lot of math.
You left them in there.
- Oh-hh.
- Hey, don't worry, Mr. P.
We got you.
Hey, Donut!
- Yo, yeah.
- Donut's crazy with cars.
He can open anything.
- Hey. What up, man?
- Hey.
Yo, he locked
his keys in there.
It's okay,
I can call AAA.
Oh, no problem, chief.
Feel the need
to work them corners, huh?
I'm just asking 'cause you don't need
to be doing what you're doing.
I need to learn some shit
on my own.
I'm trying
to help you, Sherrod,
but you making it
so I can't.
I didn't even know
the man who beat on you, Bubs.
He was short money
on the corner.
I swear he wasn't
nothing to me.
Yeah, but when the shit start,
there's nothing to be done, right?
What would I have done
if he started whaling on you?
Same kind of nothing, see?
That's how the corners be.
They going to use you up,
Sherrod.
You welcome to stay tonight, but you
ain't in school tomorrow morning,
this partnership need
to be done.
These two precincts
are the bellwether for the Fifth.
If you can take even 18%
out of Carcetti in these,
it's a good guess he won't
have the numbers citywide.
And who are we ticketed
with over here?
The N.D.O.,
I hope, because...
...this amid allegations that
high-ranking police officials intervened
to have a veteran police detective
removed from the controversial case.
The Braddock murder became
a focal point in the mayoral campaign
when Councilman
Thomas Carcetti alleged
the West Baltimore man
was killed
because he was
a witness in the case.
...Because they were afraid
the police would prove
what they most fear, that
Fredro Braddock was murdered
because he was a witness,
and the city failed to protect him.
It's on all three channels.
And "The Sun" and "The Post"
are both calling for comment.
And my sources within the department say
the rank-and-file officers
are simply appalled by this blatant
political manipulation.
Damn, turn it up.
Hey, Greggs, you're famous.
...is to remove
a highly-decorated veteran
with 15 years' experience as a murder
investigator without reason...
- That'd be me.
- Then replaced with a rookie
who has yet to handle a single
homicide investigation...
- That'd be you.
-...then we need to rethink...
- The fuck I ever do to him?
You gonna make it
too heavy, yo.
It might work
if we make it bigger.
It would work if we
had balsa wood, you know?
- It's really light and strong.
- Man, you so full of--
oh, shit.
Zombie Master.
Need to take us
a little walk.
Nah, I'm good here.
Yo. Young'uns need
to move along.
Sure, Chris, we'll bump.
- Yo, Snoop, your sister in my class.
- What the fuck?
You high
or something, nigger?
You boys be
smoking that shit?
Hearing good things
about you.
Say you straight up,
take care of your people,
not begging no handouts.
Motherfucker, you hear the nigger
talking to you,
giving you praises and shit. You
standing here looking fucking stupid.
Yo, chill.
Sometimes
she get a little hot.
I'm just saying
the boy ain't right!
Yo, we always in the market
for a good soldier.
When we see one we like,
we take care of the situation--
take him in, school him,
make him family.
And if you're with us,
you're with us,
just like we'd be
with you all the way.
You have a mind,
you're in.
Look, man.
I already got a family--
my moms
and my little brother.
Yeah, heard that.
But think on it.
We'll be around
if you need something.
He saw me, yo. I knew it.
I knew Chris was asking Michael
about me.
I knew it, man.
I'm dead.
- Yo, man, good looking out.
- Yeah.
- I thought they was gonna--
- Yeah, I know, I know.
What-what he ask about me?
I know he asked about me.
- What'd you say? What'd you tell him?
- Calm down,
- it weren't even about you.
- Yo, for real,
you need to tell me.
What did he ask you?
Yo, you right, man.
Chris was all up in your business.
He down on you
for some deep shit, man.
I don't even know what.
Nah, I'm just fucking
with you, man.
He didn't even
speak your name.
Oh, man.
So, Erv, what's next? Your officers
gonna shoot a couple of tourists?
Maybe fly a helicopter
into Harbor Place?
What can we expect the last week
of my re-election campaign?
Sir, I did what you asked--
no more, no less.
Hamsterdam--
legalized drug zone?
Oh, he takes responsibility
for that.
- The subpoenas all over town.
- That, too.
Well, then the leak about the witness
murder. That was his shop too, right?
- Hell, yeah.
- And now this last thing,
transferring detectives off the case--
what is that? What is that?
- Scuttling the investigation.
- Yeah, right.
- Yeah, that's awful-- Jesus!
- Mr. Mayor, you asked me
- to slow that investigation down.
- Mm-mmm, mm-mmm.
Subtle, Ervin. Hmm?
You hold a few facts
for a few weeks.
You put a report or two
in a desk drawer.
But the transferring
of people off a case?!
Look, you told me...
you specifically
wanted me to not--
Ervin, you may leave.
- Mr. Mayor--
- That will be all, Commissioner.
Nuh-uh.
No, I need a word or two
with your deputy, Ervin.
Have a seat.
I tried to warn him.
I mean, if it leaked out of Homicide
about the dead witness,
why wouldn't it leak that we
bumped a detective?
Why didn't you come to us
beforehand?
I'm a loyal subordinate,
Mr. Mayor,
and Ervin is a good man working
under considerable pressure.
He's a hack.
You're not bothered
by the pressure, Deputy?
Not in the least.
I need you to make this
go away, Bill.
I won't forget,
believe me.
Another thing-- Slim Charles
got up with me.
Said the fat man
want a sitdown.
Nah. I did that already.
Well, Slim say the fat man knew
the card game was gonna get took.
He did, did he?
Set it up.
Why you always
be back here?
Quiet. And I can see
what comes.
But you out in the weather
and shit.
- I don't like to speak in no rooms.
- Yeah.
Yo, oh-oh,
you ain't staying long.
So you know,
I almost got that for you.
I just need
a couple of days more.
You can keep my money
for now.
- I got something that needs doing.
- Anything, Marlo-- your call.
Omar gonna come in your store,
stick it up, rob you.
You gonna call the police,
make a report. You feel me?
Yeah, that'll work, but, uh,
you know when he get out,
he's coming right at me,
I ain't scared or nothing.
- I'm just saying, you know?
- He ain't gonna get out.
A man make bail on robbery.
Make it no bail.
If you have a problem,
Iike you can't make it
to detention,
you need to tell me.
That's your responsibility.
People will be more than willing
to help you out,
but it's up to you to ask.
You can go back
to the cafeteria...
or hang up here.
Duquan,
could you come here?
I thought maybe you could help me out--
I packed too much.
Take this down
to the cafeteria
and get yourself something to drink
from the machine.
Thank you.
Crystal,
you got a second?
What's up with Duquan?
I gave him some new clothes.
I was expecting--
He might have lost them.
That fast?
It weren't that.
His people take his clothes,
sell it on the corners.
- You're kidding.
- No, sir.
Everybody knows.
Which brings me to
what we're proposing--
different kids,
different approaches.
You tell us who we need to touch
at North Avenue to get the go-ahead.
The "Puzzle Palace"?
Look, if y'all still wanna jump in
and help, I'm fine with it.
That's about all the okay
you need in my house.
The Stricker Street situation is
waiting in the office.
Neighborhood squabbles,
and my babies bring it in here.
Two fights yesterday-- all because
the mothers can't get along.
I gotta go.
Mrs. Donnelly will work out
the nuts and bolts.
But just so you hear it,
thank you.
It'll be the only time anyone
in this system will think to say it.
He's a good man.
You need to protect him.
- Protect him?
- Principal Withers
just went out on a limb for you,
and in this system they know
how to handle a chainsaw.
Excuse me?
Anyone has a problem
with what we're doing,
it's on him.
So you specified
eighth-graders?
We have 256 on roll.
241 attend
on a regular basis.
Of those, 40 or so would fit your bill
of corner kids.
40?
Pretty workable.
Ahem.
- What would you suggest?
- Start with 10 or so.
Ms. Sampson has enough
to get you going.
- One of them named Namond Brice?
- Pick of the litter.
But you'll have to wait.
He's on a three-day suspension.
Tilghman Middle School.
Can I help you?
Remember when I was a cadet,
I was up here on a cadaver search.
Instructor gets
on the radio to say,
"We're looking for
one body in particular.
If you go grabbing
everyone you see,
we'll be here all day," he says.
Leakin Park...
where West Baltimore
brings out its dead.
Not anymore,
from the look of things.
Not by the roadside,
anyway.
If he's dumping them here,
he's dumping them
deep in the woods.
Come on.
At each raid site,
we're anticipating dope
or cash or guns.
All warrants are
for prime locations
Iinked to high-level
violators.
Weeks-old addresses linked
to low-level corner boys.
We'll also be sweeping drug corners
at these locations.
Wagons will hold
in this location here.
Jump-off time--
1500 hours.
We take our position
10 minutes before the assault here.
The go is on my say-so.
Questions? Excellent.
We'll hold in the rec room
till it's time to stage.
Warrants are one thing,
but street sweeps on Marlo Stanfield's
crews? Are you guys serious?
Carv, you give these hoodleheads
too much credit.
Trust me on this, Boy Wonder.
Never mind this horseshit.
So what've they got you
doing for your man?
Who, the lieutenant?
No, Royce. Herc, the mayor's
your meal ticket.
He gets another four years,
you're liable to wear the gold braid.
Shouldn't you be out
waving a campaign sign or some shit?
And so ends the last crusade
of the Major Crimes Unit--
with a whimper.
Lester would cry to see his wiretap
cannibalized for that crap.
Street sweeps
on Marlo Stanfield?
- So what else you got cooking?
- Narcotics cases?
C.I.D. has the Burman indictment
coming in. Nothing past that.
As wars go, this drug thing
seems to rate less and less.
If Demper wins and manages
to forgive my trespasses,
maybe I'll go in and beg
for something new.
I don't know. Just feels like
enough's enough.
Crutchfield, line two, lntake.
- Sergeant, you were looking for me?
- I was, yeah.
Curly fry?
Chicken doohickey?
Sit down.
Norris is back
on the Braddock case.
It's by order
of the deputy ops.
In fact, we're gonna go
with a story that says
he was never off the case,
that you and he are partnered,
a task force of two,
working it together.
Fuck you, fat man.
Not original, but succinct.
I like your approach.
Y'all humiliate me once
by dropping me into this thing,
and now you're gonna shame me again
by bringing Norris back.
This is Homicide, Detective.
This is not some boiler room unit
where no one pays attention
to whatever the fuck it is
you call police work.
The bosses?
They know our names up here.
Now I didn't like it
when they came to me
and told me to dump Norris,
but dump him I did.
And it's not like I wanna
carry water for them
now that they're pretending
they never told me to do any such thing,
but carry the water I will.
And in the end,
when everyone else in this unit
is buried and beshitted,
this detective sergeant
will still be standing.
So get the story straight:
Norris was always
the primary,
and you are now assisting
on an investigation
which is progressing
even as we speak.
Does the colonel
know about this?
He's in the hospital--
chemo didn't work.
Press conference is upstairs
in half an hour.
- So don't be late.
- Press conference?
Mm-hmm.
I ain't mean
to laugh at you none.
I know it sound crazy,
but I ain't joking.
For real, Lex a zombie.
I knew it way before
what Na' and them was saying.
Listen,
they had me tell Lex to go up
to the playground.
I told him to go up there
and see some girl.
He ain't never come
back down.
So what they gonna do to me
when they get mad at me?
It makes sense Chris taking them
into the vacants--
to change them.
And you know what else?
That ain't
what he doing--
Chris in the vacants.
Changing them?
He ain't changing them,
he killing them.
That's all.
They're getting killed.
How you know?
Can't tell nobody.
I seen it.
I seen them walk
a boy up into one house
over there on Calhoun.
You seen that?
Yeah.
That's just false.
Detective Norris has been
working in this case nonstop.
And given her narcotics
expertise,
Detective Greggs
was assigned to augment
rather than to replace him.
But for two days sources
inside the department were saying--
I'm inside the department,
and I'm telling you that's not true.
We do not play politics
with a criminal investigation.
And how do you explain
Councilman Gray's allegations?
I think you should ask
Councilman Gray that question.
- Police! Search warrant!
- Take the back.
- On the ground, now!
- Police! Search warrant!
Two upstairs.
- Don't move!
- Check that backroom.
I said, get your ass
on the ground.
- Get down!
- This is the 1300 block, right?
- No, this is the 12.
Are we on the right corner?
- We had this as a stash house?
- According to the wiretap.
How long ago?
They move them around, you know.
- Zeroes on the warrants.
- Minor arrests
- on the designated corners, sir.
- They were tipped!
- You think?
- For us to come up this empty
at all these locations,
it has to be.
This cocksucker Marlo thinks
he's smarter than us?
He is not. Sergeant, I want
to know where he hangs.
You mean like him personally?
He moves around,
Lieutenant. He floats.
But I have seen him
in the concrete park behind Fulton.
- In a park?
- If the weather's right, he sits
out there in some lawn chairs,
holds court.
He's got people covering
every approach
so there's no creeping up on him. My
guess is that he likes to talk outdoors
so no one can drop
a microphone on him.
Sergeant, what can
we do with that?
I admit I've made
some mistakes,
Burrell being
one of the biggest.
But he's got a job
for about 10 more days.
After the primary,
he's gone, believe me.
And that last stunt--
pulling a detective.
- What'd you expect?
- Not that-- huh-uh.
Hey, I had nothing to do
with that nonsense.
Now, that's a straight-up lie. I was
at that damn meeting when you told him,
- "Slow the case down."
- I didn't mean--
Who the hell knows
what you mean anymore, Clarence?
Look at this.
Look at it!
You gave me
your word on this--
your word, Clarence.
But here you are ticketed up
with Eunetta in her best precincts
and then ticketed up
with my girl Daniels
where she's
running strong.
Odell, this is the first
I've seen this.
Come on, now! This is probably
Eunetta's people pulling this shit.
With a "Citizens for Royce"
authority line?
Eh, look at you, Clarence.
Just look at you.
You've forgotten your agenda.
You've forgotten your base.
You think a shave
and some Marcus Garvey posters
are gonna get you over?
Do you think that's gonna
make up for jumping in bed
with every damn
developer?
Shit. You're even
on Clay Davis's tit.
Now don't you go getting
all self-righteous with me, Odell.
Campaign runs on dollars--
you know it.
Whose dollars?! Those sons of bitches
you got around your card table
every month feeding your kitty?
Oh, yeah,
I know about that too.
You-- trouble with you--
fuck you, Clarence. I'm gonna
sit what's left of this one out.
- I'm gonna sit it out.
- Sit it out.
- The primary?
- Sit it out!
Odell!
Who the hell do you
think you are, huh?
Come November, I'm still gonna be
the only game in town!
Odell, turn your back on me now,
I won't forget!
We can't afford this.
We need his organization on Tuesday.
- Go after him!
- Fuck that
holier-than-thou
motherfucker!
Delegate Watkins.
Delegate Watkins!
Wait, sir.
I-I'm sure we can
work this out.
You and the mayor
can talk this through.
Deputy Rawls, please.
It's Lieutenant Hoskins
at the Hall.
You're gonna use the hole
in the wall, right?
Yeah, I'm gonna rub some dogshit
on the front of this thing.
I don't want nobody
touching it.
Got it?
You need
to raise it a bit.
Yeah, that's good.
Right there, that works.
- Thought I heard something.
- Rats.
- How we doing?
- We need to go.
He ain't nothing
but a skanky-ass bitch to begin with.
And besides,
he ex-police.
So you know what that like.
I'm going to the ladies' room.
Bey, you need to talk to him.
Visiting hours
end in 30 minutes.
- Visiting hours...
- Yo, Daddy, don't even go there,
with you all the time telling me
how you dropped out in the sixth grade,
went up on the corner
with Avon and Stringer,
earned cheese for the family, saying
how it made you a man--
All right, all right.
You right.
Can't throw rocks.
But I'm just saying,
you know how your mother be,
with all the fussing.
Maybe you just need to slow it up.
You know what I'm saying?
Yo, you heard
how Marlo punked Bodie?
Said he either got to work for him
or give up his corner.
Don't you know?
His sorry ass buckled.
Oh-hh, you'd have gone
about it different?
Yeah, I'd have
stood tall, like you.
Got my nine--
fuck Chris and them.
Listen to you,
all spit and fire.
You'd have gone to the mattress
all by your lonesome
and went up against
half of the West side.
You got it where it counts,
and I respect that more than anything.
But shit out there now ain't like
it was when we was coming up.
Back in the day, a punk nigger
like Marlo steps out,
breaking the rules and shit, he find
himself in the back of a car trunk
on the way to Leakin Park.
No doubt.
We did that shit right.
Word was your bond.
Man looked out for his own,
knowing he in a family.
Dig where
I'm coming from?
But today
it's all fucked up.
These steps.
- Thank you, baby.
- You're good to go.
Say "Omar."
Omar.
Nothing?
We checked both sides
of the street
- from here up to Monroe.
- Nothing?
Nothing that don't
belong in no sewer.
Thanks.
Other ideas?
Whoo!
Blood, bump me off that nigger
up the "skreet."
Motherfucker
in the "Bruick"?
That be him.
I be saying,
no motherfucker gonna
run off with my "hairon."
Oh, this is
fucking great.
Get somebody who reads lips,
this motherfucker's history.
Is this legal-- I mean,
intercepting what they're saying?
Don't go Freamon on me.
Shit. I got to run.
Hey, man, what about some
fucking relief? I been here all morning!
You heard?
They making movies.
Yeah. How you
wanna play it?
I ain't sure.
Let's see the fat man.
How'd the other thing
turn out?
All good.
- Yo.
- What up, boy?
- If you want some, I got Reeses.
- Nah, man.
You trying to make
some real cheese? $5?
- What you need?
- Me and Paul gonna get it on with Tiff.
Keep an eye out. I don't want Mrs. D
creeping up. Feel me?
I feel you, but I got some sixth-graders
waiting on a special order.
Let them wait, man.
It ain't like we gonna be all day.
All right.
No, ma'am, it says right here--
His Honor had the Bureau of Solid Waste
conduct a clean sweep
along Tivoly.
But it took six months
before they showed up.
Well yeah, okay,
but nobody's perfect.
But hey, listen. I wouldn't be
sitting here if I didn't believe
Clarence Royce wasn't truly committed
to this city and its people.
What about the crime
in our neighborhood?
I admit that's another
good point.
But, lady,
between you and me, I can tell
from your voice you're black and
you can tell from my voice I'm white.
So I gotta ask you,
when do you think the last time
a white man voted for a black man
when there was another
white man in the race?
I don't know, but you must
really believe in him.
Well, ain't that what I been saying?
He's just the best candidate.
- So you'll go with my man?
- I'll think about it.
All right, that's great.
Thank you for your time.
- Goodbye.
- All right.
- I have a hall pass.
- Yeah, good for you.
- Mine's down.
- Attaboy.
You need bodies, Lester?
Here you go.
We got a warrant and a teletype
for my boy Lex.
So dead or alive, he's on file.
And beyond that,
it's time for you to shine
that mighty intellect of yours
on some real murders, hmm?
Give up the hypotheticals
and shit.
Yeah, I suppose.
This is my issue-- crime,
and I understand completely
what you're saying.
And if you give me the opportunity,
I will be able to do something to--
to help you out and, you know,
other people in this neighborhood.
Mr. Ricks,
thank you for your time
- and for your attention.
- No problem.
- Thank you.
Pretty brazen, shaking hands
with the enemy in broad daylight.
- Werner's Deli this isn't.
- Definitely not.
Though here you are, Councilman,
leaving no door unopened.
Shoe leather--
our secret weapon.
You surprised me.
You've made this a horse race.
So uh, what makes me think you didn't
just happen by and find us here?
Watkins is breaking
with the mayor.
How do you know?
I know. I've carried the mayor's water
because I had to, Councilman.
I'd love to see some new blood
in this city.
And I'd love the chance
to do the right thing
for this police department
for a change.
Wait until he turns
the corner.
District office for Watkins--
Gilmore Street.
And fuck
them red lights, man.
Not a place you expect
to find any gangsters--
police, for that matter.
- Heard you knew something I didn't.
- Told you before--
I make it my business
to keep an ear to the ground.
to do business.
We doing business,
or are we just talking?
And if it's talk,
I'ma walk.
I heard the people pulling
security at the card game
weren't too keen
on their wages.
I figured it was
only a matter of time
before they found a way
to get their due compensation.
And you didn't think
to tell me?
A man learns best
when he get burned.
How do I know you ain't
making this shit up?
You don't.
Things happen on the street.
Proof is hard to come by.
Go ahead, open it.
Off the street,
there's all kind of proof.
They planning on executing
those Friday--
time it with the election,
I guess,
show they doing their job,
cleaning up the city,
taking down a kingpin.
- How did you come by this?
- Told you before--
I keep my ear
to the ground.
- What are you gonna do with it?
- Maybe nothing.
Charlie's not part
of the co-op.
Or maybe
I tip him for a fee.
What do you think a man
with a whole lot of money
would pay
for his freedom?
You know, lately
I come to find out someone trying
to take pictures of me.
Pictures?
Video.
You heard anything about me
through your travels?
Had no incentive to listen.
You do now.
It's one thing
to sit out the primary.
It's another
for me to turn
on Clarence Royce.
- Granted.
- And if I did jump,
why not land
behind Tony Gray?
At least he's from
my side of the tracks.
Tony can't win. I can.
Look, the truth is,
whatever I can do for you,
the mayor can match or double.
I have a pretty good
grass-roots organization,
but nothing even close
to his kind of money.
Now, I'll ticket up
with anyone you want me to.
I know you want Daniels in the 11th
and Stokes in the 10th.
I'll keep away from any tickets
you think I might harm.
I know I'm not everyone's idea
of a bargain on your side of town.
- Hmm.
- But right now,
a week from the primary,
the fact is,
Royce and I both need you.
After the election, the equation changes
for him but not for me.
I'm a white mayor
in a majority-black city,
and if I'm gonna
do anything--
and, Delegate, I am so serious
about fixing this city--
I'm gonna have to govern
by consensus.
And if you support me, you will have
a voice within my administration
simply because
I'm gonna need it.
Last poll that
Clarence showed me,
he was up
by seven points.
Bullshit.
I'm within four.
- You won't be needing that.
- I know.
- Here?
- Yeah, here.
Dag.
Yo, turn it off-- the bulb
might have got too hot.
Or the battery's dying.
We should go back.
- Yo, man, it stinks, man.
- Ain't like it was.
See he ain't move.
Yeah.
Blood still stuck to his hair.
- He dead?
- He dead.
Lex too?
He dead. They all is.
Feel better?
Donut wrong, yo.
Ain't no special dead.
There's just dead.
www.tvsubtitles.net