13 bodies, all female.
11 white, two Asian-looking.
All between the ages of maybe 20, 30.
All very dead.
- From Eastern Europe, probably.
- So this is, what, an accident?
Your air pipe's up top, crushed,
probably during the off-load.
So, yeah, accidental, probably.
But that's his call, right?
- Doctor.
- Frazier.
Hey, how are we doing here?
- How are we doing?
- I mean, what are we doing?
What's the plan with all this?
- Your first death investigation, officer...?
- Russell.
- Yeah, first and onliest.
- You got 13 for the price of one.
We're gonna start cutting this afternoon. Any
identification should come through my office.
What identification? So far, we don't have
a passport or visa in the bunch.
Whatever you find in this luggage,
senditover
or they're all going
to the anatomy board as Jane does.
Who's the investigating agency?
If they were alive, they'd be illegals.
That would mean immigration.
- They're dead so they're cargo.
- But no contraband.
Nothing that's a customs violation.
- They're dead on port authority property.
- Yeah.
- That's a state thing.
- We'll eat it.
If it's accidental, then it's just
about ids on these stowaways, right?
Good enough for me, brother.
No reason to open a full case folder
that I can see.
- Wait, you cid guys are rolling out on this?
- No crime, no investigation.
All you've got right here, officer Russell,
is a lot of papen/vork.
And then there was one.
When you walk through the garden
you gotta watch your back
well, I beg your pardon
walk the straight and narrow track
if you walk with Jesus
he's gonna save your soul
you gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
he's got the fire and the fury
at his command
well, you don't have to worry
if you hold on to Jesus' hand
we'll all be safe from Satan
when the thunder rolls
we just gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
Down in the hole
down in the hole
gotta help me keep the devil
- You don't have to do this.
- No?
- Anything you'd say, I already said to spiros.
- You called him a Greek asshole?
- You think we wanted this?
- I don't know what the fuck you people want.
All I know is I got a can full of young
girls suffocating to death on my docks.
- This was a mistake.
- A mistake?
They fuckin' died in that can while this stupid
son of a bitch sat with his dick in his hands.
- You know nothing.
- We understand you're upset, frank.
We're upset, too. Sergei was supposed
to wait for a friend to come off the boat.
Our friend was supposed to tell us
that there was no problem.
- No customs.
- He did not come off the boat.
- Why the fuck not?
- We're trying to find out. We don't know.
You don't get the right message
so these girls die on my docks?
This is how it goes?
On my docks, this happened!
I understand how you feel. We're upset, too.
Everybody's upset. Nobody here wanted this.
Uncle frank,
they're saying it wasn't on purpose.
You could've told me
there were girls in that fucking can
so I didn't shove them back in the stacks
like I did.
Why didn't you tell me
what was in that motherfucking can?
Now you want to know what's in the cans?
Before you wanted to know nothing,
now you ask.
Guns, ok?
Drugs, whores, vodka, bmws.
Beluga caviar or bombs maybe. Hm?
- Bad terrorists with big nuclear bombs.
- Whoosh!
I'm kidding you, frank, it's a joke.
But you don't ask...
Because you don't want to know.
The next time the Greek's got something
breathing in them cans, I need to know it.
Uh-uh. Give him a couple of days, you know?
- So Roberto been caught?
- Yep, DEA got him in New York.
Now this shit makes some sense.
The money we sent
for the last go-round came back.
Damn, they ain't gonna touch us now?
Dominicans are running scared,
acting like we the problem.
Roberto won't see us.
Stringer had to go to the lawyer up there.
They saying they have to be sure
before they get back with us.
- You only got seven years...
- So they think I'm a snitch?
They ain't saying they think it. They just
don't know how the feds got to Roberto.
- So we on the outside.
- Yep.
Look... we hanging onto them projects
with scraps.
Avon, you gotta have somebody for us.
A friend in Atlanta
own a rim shop, name of vargus.
Have string fly down there tomorrow
to meet him.
You seen d'Angelo lately?
He on the j-tier, you know what I mean? It's
very difficult for me to get over there.
So you ain't checking on him
and donette's out and about.
- I don't know what's what.
- What's up with donette?
- I leave messages, she ain't calling back.
- She ain't had her ass down here regular.
We need to tighten shit up. She should be
bringing his son by every week.
- Yeah, I'm gonna put stringer on that, too.
- After all he has done for us,
Dee needs to be cared for, avon.
- Promises were made.
- I know.
He took the 20, he ain't complaining, but he
is carrying a lot of weight for this family.
We keeping him close.
Dee being cold toward me right now.
- He in here trying to make adjustments.
- Adjustments?
Brianna, you know damn well I ain't
gonna let shit happen to him, right?
- You got these off the boat?
- What, in winter?
In a couple of months. Fringe benefit.
Can't catch crabs in homicide, right?
Except the occasional emergency room nurse
every now and again.
- Whoo. Need some air in here.
- Leave it, leave it, leave it.
I don't need the hassle
if rawls comes past.
You're not the run-of-the-mill
kind of asshole.
- You're the special kind of asshole.
- I'm special, all right.
How long did it take you to figure out the
tide took that girl over the county line?
- Three hours.
With your harbor maps and tide tables.
Just to stick rawls with an extra body.
Never mind that you fucked Cole
with a stone whodunnit.
- That's collateral damage.
- Yeah?
You gonna waste that crab gut?
You're a pussy, besides, Jimmy.
We, uh... we need Omar, Jimmy.
You see this?
- 13 girls?
- Yeah, I heard about it.
- Who caught it?
- It ain't ours.
Port police has jurisdiction over patapsco.
Ain't gonna be a murder either
so who gives a fuck?
Jimmy, I ain't got no case on bird unless
that crazy motherfucker Omar testifies.
You hear me?
It's time you showed bunk the love.
- You want love, you come and sit on my lap.
- Shit.
This motherfucker tells me the customs seal
got broke on the dock and I'm responsible.
Can you fucking believe that? I seen it
on the crane, the seal's already broke.
- Who got to it?
- The crew probably, some goddamn seaman.
- What was it?
- Vodka, I think.
I ain't saying we didn't squeeze a case or
two, but, fuck it, the can was already open.
I didn't come to the union hall today
on no bread truck.
I swear, frank,
we grabbed a couple of cases at the end.
- After all them sailors damn near raped it.
- Couple of cases?
Yeah, it was... four, yeah.
- What the fuck is up with the police?
- What?
They're stroking tickets
on every fucking car.
"Rear tag not entirely visible"?
- You got the tow bar set high.
- "Emergency access blocked." You kidding?
We've been parking this side of the
building since fucking ships had sails.
Come on, pal, what the fuck?
- It ain't me, it's my boss.
- Who's your boss?
- Valchek, southeast district.
- Stan valchek?
The district commander, yeah.
That sawed-off piece of shit.
Why's he fucking with us?
Whatever it's about,
you definitely got the man's attention.
Word comes down from my lieutenant,
we're to ride past your union
hall twice a day and paper cars.
- You work for a gaping asshole.
- More than one, actually.
We're not gonna put up with this shit,
we'll go downtown.
Take it all the way to the mayor's office,
I can't blame you, but leave me out of it.
It's chain of command.
I gotta live with the
son of a bitch, too, right?
- You can't tell me this place ain't clean.
- You talk when I say you can.
Turnkey! Fuck you all!
Who told you to decorate, nigger?
Turnkey!
Cell looks fucked-up to me.
What you calling clean?
- Man, I ain't done shit.
- Don't say that to me, motherfucker!
Pets, too?
No, you see, they plastic.
They got little motors and all, man.
Clean this shit before lock-down.
That's four in a row, bitch!
Turnkey!
Wait here, this won't take long.
What do you want?
He's an e-rate, you're a g.
He wants the ship, he gets it. Seniority,
mimms. Ain't no union without it, brother.
- Your sweetheart's out there.
- Who?
I gotta go, mimms. I got to.
- Kind of empty in here.
- Everyone's working.
- You getting the message?
- Message?
I had people working on a window
for the nave
up St. casimir's since
easter, you know that?
I took money from half a dozen people,
told them where it was gonna go.
- You tell father lewandowski?
- I was gonna surprise him.
Yeah, you surprised everybody.
Now there's one window too many.
Here's the thing, father lew says
he could take another window
in the rectory on the second floor.
- Good for you.
- No, good for you, frank.
If you don't want my finger in your eye,
you'd better do what's right here.
What's right, huh?
What's right would be for you to come here
like a decent human being
and ask a common courtesy,
but that's not you, it's not your way.
My old man said you were a half-ass punk
over at holy redeemer as a kid.
My sister said you were a pain in the ass
at them cyo dances
where girls wouldn't look at you.
Damn near everyone said,
when you got your badge,
it was too much for anybody named valchek
to have a patrolman's drag.
Sure enough, you've been an
official asshole every day since.
Fuck you! And your window!
- Where are you gonna be?
- I'm gonna find some lunch somewhere.
- Give me an hour, yeah?
- Yeah.
- Hey. What the fuck is this?
- A knot.
Why don't you just do bunny ears?
So what else we got?
Medics, clothes, bedroll, that's it.
- Here's a letter, though.
- A letter? What language?
Who knows?
Same backwards-ass writing, though.
That's like Russian or something,
I'm telling you.
I know. Can't figure the name or the
address, but the stamp says "magyar" on it.
- Where's magyar?
- What the hell do I look like, rand McNally?
Hey.
Which detective caught all the dead girls?
- Detectives? They're at the bar already.
- These yours?
They chalked it up as an accidental
and dumped the papennork on us.
She found them, she writes on it.
- I'm mcnulty, city marine unit.
- Beatrice Russell.
- Got any ids yet?
- No visas or passports.
A few scraps of paper,
but nothing to make sense of.
Russian alphabet on most of it.
You just curious?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Day before yesterday,
I fished out a Jane Doe near the bridge.
No missing person report filed.
We got 14 bedrolls and 13 bodies.
- Mine was a murder.
- Murder? You're kidding me.
We got some photos if
you wanna take a look.
I called down the morgue.
They say the dental work isn't local.
Overseas, they think.
- That your girl?
- Think so. She looks better here.
- You got her in the water out by the bridge?
- 0900 hours, by the fort armistead dock.
Why would a murdered girl be in the water
and the rest suffocating in a can?
- What went wrong?
- Air pipe up top got crushed.
Happened when cargo shifted around,
most likely.
They had cargo up front of the container
with a false back after 25 feet.
You had cartons stacked in front, but a tight
passage to a small door in the false wall.
Opens from the outside only.
- They're in here the whole trip?
- Probably not.
Once they're at sea, usually someone in
the crew is in on it, you know, a Shepherd.
He lets them out to eat, move around,
use the bathroom, whatever.
They were clawing at the wall for air. That's
what the medical examiner said, anyway.
- Where's the air pipe?
- That's the hole. Pipe's up top.
- You get a lot of stowaways?
- Some.
Usually it's customs
or ins that finds them.
Most are Dominicans or Haitians
or from that part of the world, anyway.
- Not so much from Europe?
- A bit more since 9/11, actually.
I think because people can't get in on visas
anymore like they used to. There you go.
Usually, the Shepherd tries to put
a can like this on bottom of the stack
so they can pop it and the girls
walk out on the floor of the hold.
Where was this one?
- Look.
- What?
- That look right to you?
- What do you mean?
- You said you were with the marine unit?
- Yeah.
What does the marine unit
have to do with dead girls in a can?
Not a thing.
- What do you want me to do?
- You can go to father lew.
Ask him to give sobotka back his money.
Switch the windows, maybe.
You ever in your life
seen a priest give money back?
The guy pays for a
window, he gets a window.
- I thought you had suction.
- At city hall and in Annapolis, I got suction.
But who but the pope has any drag
with the cardinal? Get over it.
- How the fuck's he get that kind of money?
- Now, that's a good question.
I mean, the whole ibs
can't have 1,500 guys left in this town
and there ain't a hundred checkers.
They got the car ships coming in.
That roll-on/roll-off cargo's
keeping them afloat.
- That's all they got?
- Pretty much.
Past six months, ibs hired Bruce dibiago's
people to lobby for them down in Annapolis.
They've been good
with political contributions.
- Throwing around a lot of cash.
- How can they?
You tell me. Dibiago does not come cheap.
- This is real money we're talking.
- You know what I think?
I think Francis sobotka's into some dirt.
You're the cop, not me.
The grainery?
So I hear burrell's gonna be
the next police commissioner.
Yeah, I've seen worse.
If it's crushed by another container,
it should've been one movement.
Two if something shifts, then shifts back.
This looks like someone's been pounding
on it in a bunch of spots. See?
Before I rule it, I wanna go down
with a metallurgist to be sure.
But, yeah, from the look of it,
you just bought yourself 13 homicides.
Congratulations.
If the commissioner goes to Washington,
it's you, right?
That's for the mayor to decide.
I'd have to clear the council, too.
If the mayor wants
you, that's not a problem.
You been around as long as me,
you make a few enemies.
The first district guys?
They're not gonna start nothing.
- They're pushing shipley.
- See, that's racist.
You know, it personally offends me
that anybody would reach down past you
to elevate some colonel
just because he happens to be white.
Know what I'll do?
I'm gonna phone my friends at the hall.
That'll bring the first district in line.
That's very kind. What, if anything, is
there that I can do for you, major valchek?
Funny you should ask. I need a detail.
Cid people mostly, though I can spare
some bodies out of my district.
What for?
Some guys in the southeast
are showing a lot of money.
- Port guys, longshoremen.
- Lbs?
I'm not talking about
going after the union.
Just a couple of guys
in one local that look fat.
Drugs, maybe, or the usual thieving.
- Frank sobotka. You heard the name?
- No.
I'm not saying
the problem even goes past him.
- What's he to you, Stan?
- To me?
Hmm.
He's an asshole.
Six men for six weeks.
Rawls will pick them.
You ordered more than you ate.
It's cold out here.
Cedric, I shouldn't have
brought it up again. I'm sorry.
You're right. You're always right.
I'm just saying you have to be realistic.
You did what you did
and now you are where you are.
In the basement.
If they buried you any deeper,
you'd be under the damn building.
- Burrell won't be there forever.
- Burrell will be the next police commissioner.
And you know it.
But you've got the law degree.
With your police experience, half a
dozen firms would think you're a prize.
You've got options.
- Just because they don't...
- You're right, you're right.
I'll put in my papers.
- Who wants breakfast?
- Christ, it's about time.
Luckie's was closed. I
had to go to the Metro.
Hope he got the brown eggs.
I thought mutt'd be working north point
today. He like them ro-ro ships.
His wife is having some kind of operation.
He gave back his hours.
- Who got them?
- New Charles works for mutt.
Yo, zig. You working today?
No. Came here to have breakfast
with you duper-faced fucks.
Most important goddamn meal
of the goddamn day, right?
- Set them up, Dolores, zig is thirsty.
- That's right, I'm thirsty.
You know what?
Bottoms up, you ugly whores.
- Yo, Nick.
- What's up?
Come here.
- I got a line on something.
- Oh, yeah?
- You know white Mike from down Curtis bay?
- Yeah.
- He's gonna stake me to a package.
- A package?
Dope, Nicky, dope.
I got work today.
I'll make as much money not working,
see what I'm saying?
- So why the fuck you coming to me?
- I want you to come in on it with me.
You bring a little cash,
my man might give us a bigger package.
We turn it around, we both get paid.
Ship's in, gentlemen.
- Fuck that shit, zig.
- Time to work.
- Nicky, come on, man.
- All right I ride with you?
Will you think about it?
Dolores, can I get another shot?
- What's up?
- Dwi checkpoint.
Step out of the car for a breathalyzer.
Who the... it's eight in
the goddamn morning.
Who the... who the fuck gets drunk
at eight in the morning?
Sir.
Bill, I'm not arguing that the
jurisdiction's not technically ours.
Patapsco's port authority property.
The port police have jurisdiction.
- That's not in dispute here.
- Good.
They're not equipped for
a death investigation.
You dump 13 bodies on them,
you're dumping them on us.
Msp is gonna have to pick up that slack,
overburdened as we are.
Robbie, I have fought and scratched
and clawed for four months
to get my clearance rate up above 50%
and right now it stands at exactly 51 .6%.
Do you know what my clearance rate will be if
I take 13 whodunnits off your hands? 39.4%.
- Bill, like I told you...
- We did not get to be colonels
by being complete fucking idiots, right?
Robbie, you poor bastard,
you look like you need a cup of coffee.
That's what I'm talking about.
Whoo!
The man is a god.
- Yo, big chief.
- Hmm.
Gotta get him back
to maximum security by six, all right?
Yeah. Come on in, man.
Sit down. Fix yourself something to eat.
- No, man, lain't hungry, late.
- What?
- No.
- You crazy? This is good shit, man.
- Better get in this.
- No.
Look, man...
If he tearing your room down, man,
we keep bringing more stuff in.
It's gonna get
so he can't tear it down fast enough.
He fucked with my fish though, I don't...
He ain't have to go there, man.
- What's up with this motherfucker?
- Remember ladontay?
Burner from over the poe homes? Caught
him at carver parking lot after school?
- We did that?
- Tilghman was ladontay's cousin.
He found out I ate the charge,
he busting my chops.
Ladontay? I can't even remember that one.
You need a score card
to keep up with your lethal ass.
Avon, he fixing to stay in my shit.
Listen, I'm gonna talk to him, all right?
I'm gonna set it straight. All right?
- What's his name again?
- Tilghman. He work the day shift on j-tier.
- I seen him around.
- Man, all these co's are fronting and shit.
You got guards bringing your meals in.
This punk motherfucker tilghman
acting righteous,
but he bringing shit in here,
steady slinging on the side.
Don't fret. All right?
It's nothing. I'm gonna take care of it.
The city won't take it?
It's port authority
property. State jurisdiction.
So it's msp out of pikesville.
The case needs real murder police.
- You just wanna fuck rawls, don't you?
- Absolutely. What can you give me?
- This is about fucking over your boss?
- If they don't eat the cases, then you will.
- What do you need?
- First, how big was the false compartment?
13 by7by7.
Ok, we got 13 adult females
breathing at a normal to elevated rate.
That's 0.25 liters of oxygen per minute...
Per victim.
- He's a doctor?
- State bureau of mines.
- Minds?
- Mines.
Officer tilghman. Officer tilghman,
I was wondering if I could parlay with you.
- Barksdale, right?
- Yeah.
- I want to know if you can help me...
- No.
- Pardon me?
- I said no, motherfucker.
Off the steps.
What the fuck are you up to now?
You're deep into somebody's shit, mcnulty.
I can tell.
This is bullshit.
Those computations were confirmed
by the medical examiner's office.
They're accurate for time of death
to within a three-hour window.
- So you say.
- Your marine unit man did the measurements.
I happen to know my marine unit man
intimately.
He is, without a doubt, the most swollen
asshole in American law enforcement.
I am not eating 13 murders. No, sir.
If they were dead when the container hit
the dock, they were murdered on board ship.
That means Baltimore county or Anne
arundel on the other side of the bridge.
If they're further down the bay,
you fellows with coast guard can take it.
This is not a city problem.
Talk amongst yourselves.
One of you is taking this case home.
No, bill, the Atlantic light passed
the key bridge at 2300 hours
and laid up at anchor, 2,000 yards off
patapsco until 0600, when it docked.
- By the map, that's Baltimore city.
- That put the ship in yourjurisdiction
for the three-hour window
for the time of death.
Bill, you look like
you could use a good cup of coffee.
Yo! Mikey. What's up?
- No.
- No, what?
No fucking way, you rat-faced piece of
shit, you fucked up the last two packages.
Mikey, look, man, that wasn't me.
You got money, you can buy a little weight.
You got no money, go fuck yourself.
- Mike, I thought we was friends.
- Did you fuck up the last two packages?
- Sort of.
- Are you beat to shit?
- No.
- Take a walk, my friend.
- What's up, man?
- What's up, playboy?
That thing in Atlanta, it's settled
for now. So we got that, you know.
Good, but I ain't called you down for that.
We got a co in here with some bullshit.
- Who?
- Name is tilghman.
He kin to that boy that wee-bey
dusted down over in that school lot.
He can't let go of that shit.
- Tilghman, huh?
- Right.
Listen, Brianna reminded me, man.
We got promises we got to keep.
I know, I heard.
You need to get with Dee's girl. Have her
bring that young 'UN down here regular.
- She need to step up and do her fucking part.
- All right.
How's Dee taking it?
He gonna do what need to be done, man,
know what I'm saying?
Dee need a little help
now and again, but...
He not out of reach or
nothing like that, right?
- No, nothing like that.
- You sure?
- He's carrying a lot of weight for us, man.
- Stringer, he's family, man.
All right? He's family.
Come on, Jimmy. Take it to the head, baby.
- Come on.
- Tell her you were first in line.
- That's it.
- There it is.
- One more, baby.
- There you go.
- That's enough.
- No, no, no, no.
You gotta do all 14 of them bad boys!
One for every member of the deer family
you gave to Cole.
Here's to ray Cole, a fine detective
and a goodly man.
Hear, hear!
Jimmy, the look on Jay landsman's face -
he nearly fucking cried!
And rawls!
Rawls, I swear to god,
the man stayed in his office all day.
All afternoon.
He just stayed there with the door closed.
- Careful, you're giving me an erection!
- Come on, now.
Motherfucker,
you have outdone yourself this time. Shit!
You ain't never coming back from this,
you know that.
Lester, what the fuck can they do to me they
haven't done? I'm riding the goddamn boat.
Fuck it, I don't give a shit.
Here's to Jane Doe 13.
All right.
11 more years
of whatever bullshit they throw at me.
I'm gonna put in my papers,
take the pension and walk.
Yeah.
11's a long time to be on the shelf.
Tell me about it, Mr. 13 years.
And four months.
Fuck it.
They can chew you up,
but they gotta spit you back out.
- 14.
- He did it.
- Fuck.
- Whoa!
Motherfucker, I ain't picking up that shit.
Go that way, go that way. Go that way.
- Hey, man, anybody still in there?
- They're keeping la-ia.
He had an old warrant on him.
- For what?
- I don't know. Some traffic shit, man.
The bondsman's inside
trying to get it all figured out.
Man, what the fuck was this all about,
anyway?
- Jerking us around.
- It's a beef I got with a police boss.
- Charlie valchek's little pissant brother.
- You gotta get that taken care of, man.
- I mean, this shit is out of hand.
- I'm gonna take care of it.
- Hey, y'all need a lift?
- Yeah.
- I'll see you.
- All right, talk good.
That runt wants a war, he's got one.
Not supposed to be talking, anyway.
- Bunk, Lester.
- Yeah?
- You two winners are on the Jane does.
- What? We're not up, Jay.
We caught that double in pimlico last week.
Cole's gonna take the double.
You two got pussy in a can.
Jay, that ain't right.
You know what ain't right?
Our squad has a negative clearance rate
for the year. A negative rate.
Now, I'm not saying ray Cole
isn't a good detective,
but I need those 14 cases to go black
so I got my best people on it.
Lay it on them.
Name and number of the port cop
who processed the scene.
And the best of luck to you
in all your future endeavors, detectives.
Motherfucker.
Beatrice Russell. Is she pretty, at least?
Last night you were too drunk to fuck.
Today you're too hung over.
What's the most useless thing on a woman?
- What?
- A drunken irishman.
Mmm.
But you're not really Irish, are you?
I had 14 shots of Jameson.
How's that for green?
You're green, all right.
You're also an idiot. Who has 14 shots?
You're a child, mcnulty.
Ow. Come here.
Come here, come here.
Show up at two in the morning again
without invitation, I will call the cops.
Why would you wanna do that?
Jimmy.
Am iyour girlfriend? No. Your wife? No.
Your soul mate? No.
What the fuck am I, Jimmy?
We're good together.
Answer the question.
I've been honest with you. My wife wants to put
it back together again, I'm gonna go for it.
You know, what with the kids and all.
You got any aspirin?
For Christ's sake,
Ronnie, I'm dying in here.
A real police department
would have an elevator.
So are you Russell? Bunk moreland.
Lester freamon.
I'm still on hold with the coast guard,
Delaware river detachment.
- What do we know?
- Atlantic light is in Philly,
heading for port of Elizabeth tonight.
I'm trying to get them to hold her.
- Anyone from your cid working this?
- Nope.
There was an argument overjurisdiction
and your colonel made everybody mad.
- All you get is me.
- Still on hold?
We can call this in from the road.
You with city homicide?
You must know Jimmy mcnulty.
Yeah, he's dead to us.
- Gentlemen, make yourselves at home.
- I've seen worse.
Leased by the highway authority,
but we can use it for an off-site.
- Furnace work?
- It does. And the phone lines.
You'll need window units
if you're here come summer,
but somehow I got a feeling that you gents
will put together a case quicker than that.
Now, this here is my district investigator,
Roland pryzbylewski.
Kid's a prodigy.
Anything you need from me, you go to him.
Gentlemen, the target is frank sobotka
and anyone frank
sobotka does his dirt with.
Roland will fill you in on the details.
Good hunting.
So, who signs the overtime slips?
Son of a bitch. You are a fucking thief!
This is where our taxes go!
- I do good work.
- Let's get it on the fucking can.
Horseface, you son of a bitch!
Christ, I'm gonna bust
the only nut I got left.
Come on, boys. Ain't no heavier
than the pallets we usually handle.
Finishing touch, boys.
Bon voyage.
- There she goes.
This area's restricted.
Yes, sir, no problem.
- Amir, Amir, why don't we sail?
- They're holding the ship.
- Who?
- Coastguard, the Americans.
Fuck, Sergei, you almost break my hand!
Bring him up!
- Have a good day, officer.
- Ok, I'll see you.
Yo. Yo, yo.
- Get up in there.
- Last call before lock-down.
All right.
Make it snappy now.
- How do you like that?
- It's good, baby, it's beautiful.
Smooth.
- Nice?
- Most def, man.
Man, watch your back, be good, baby.
- What up, man?
- Yeah, he left that in here.
- How you doing?
- All right.
Yeah?
Me and you gonna need to talk.
- Who's on board?
- 38 in the crew.
14 yemeni, eight Sri Lankan.
There are five Filipinos and the rest
are from here, there, and back again.
Anybody speak English?
With what you're asking them about, I'll
be amazed if any of them manages a word.
- Where's your captain?
- At the coast guard office.
Angry because
we're due on a New Jersey pier tomorrow.
Ain't gonna make it.
I gotta tell you, every day that you hold
us costs the shipping agent $100,000.
- The Atlantic light is a huge enterprise.
- The Atlantic light is a crime scene.
Don't try to play tough guy.
I'm not the one getting my ass kicked.
Talk to me!
Tell me what I need to know.
- Please.
- Get him up.
- Talk about the girls.
- No girls, nothing.
No English.
You no speak English,
but you know how to run.
Why you run from ship, huh?
What the fuck that supposed to mean?
Ahh.
They got him in Philadelphia.
He jumped when
the coast guard was gonna hold the ship.
- What is he?
- Sergei says he looks like an arab.
He don't know nothing.
But you kept hitting him anyway.
Get his clothes.
Fuma?
If you don't mind, I'm gonna have one.
Vocé fala portugués?
Farsi?
Come on, let's talk.
- No English.
- Tell me what happened to the girls.
No... no English.
No speak.
What, then? What do you speak?
Come on, talk to me, friend.
Turkish, huh?
You got that little hook on your nose.
Don't worry, patrioti.
I got nothing against the Turks.
That's the old world. This is the new.
- Sam.
- I don't know nothing about...
- You know.
And you're going to tell me about it, too.
After that, you're done.
I give you my word.
We popped the can to let them take a bath,
get some fresh air.
You gotta understand, my crew, they
been pulling on their pootsos for weeks.
These girls, they looked pretty good.
Yes.
The men had cash to spend.
- I saw chance for business, but that was all.
- What happened?
One of the puttanas decided
she didn't want to be a puttana no more.
This one guy got rough with her.
The whore died.
The other ones saw. I
didn't know what to do.
- You killed one, then you killed them all.
- No, that was another man.
Another man. What man?
The one girl -
they saw, they knew.
Relax.
I gave you my word.
- Watch your shoes.
- Agh! Goddamn turko.
Bleeds like a lamb.
In a year, each whore would bring
a quarter million. What is that?
$4 million.
Gone.
Anyway, there'll be other girls.
This one.
No fingerprints. No face.
That's not a problem.
English sdh