Freezing my balls off.
It ain't so bad. Loosen up.
Couple more months, it's gonna be spring.
Spnng, huh?
Listen, you gotta realize the bosses
did you a favor sending you down here.
- Citywide to marine unit.
- 7672. Go ahead.
Distress call from a private craft.
60-foot white vessel. Engines are dead.
What's the location, citywide?
In the channel near the bridge.
About 2,000 yards off the armistead pier.
10-4, we're responding.
My father used to work there.
- Beth steel?
- In the shipyards, yeah.
I had an uncle who was a supervisor there.
Got laid off in '78, though.
'73 for my dad.
- Party boat?
- Pretty one.
- More than one engine.
- Probably an electrical problem.
Is that a police boat?
How are you tonight? Good to see you.
Henry, how are you?
- Drink?
- No, thanks.
- You're the captain?
- Yeah. Harbor master?
No, city police.
- So you're dead in the water?
- Think it's the starter.
- You're not a mechanic?
- Me? No.
I can't tell the aft from the stern.
Best I can offer you is a tow line.
Claude, they're gonna need a pull.
- 10-4, we'll tow to Henderson's.
- That'll work.
Any chance you can hold off on bringing
us in? Lot of party going on now.
Wouldn't wanna cut it short
for engine trouble.
You're in the shipping channel.
Tow us somewhere out of the way
and the band plays on a while longer?
When you walk through the garden
you gotta watch your back
well, I beg your pardon
walk the straight and narrow track
if you walk with Jesus
he's gonna save your soul
you gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
he's got the fire and the fury
at his command
well, you don't have to worry
if you hold on to Jesus' hand
we'll all be safe from Satan
when the thunder rolls
we just gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
Down in the hole
down in the hole
you gotta help me keep the devil
Because...
You see what I'm saying, right?
I mean, three years in auto theft
and I didn't learn anything. I didn't care.
I'm telling you, I didn't even wanna be
a police any more. I honestly didn't.
I think that was why
I shot up my car like I did.
But this thing we did on barksdale,
the wiretap and all,
that felt like something,
that felt like something I wanna do.
So I was thinking, you know,
narcotics maybe.
- Major, you want this stuff where?
- Just in here. Up against the wall.
If there aren't any openings in the narcotics
shift, maybe assets forfeiture or something.
Hey, hey, easy, easy. Everything breaks.
I mean, with this barksdale thing.
Lester freamon had us
deep into the money, real deep.
We could've seized real estate,
cash, vehicles, all kinds of stuff.
If the bosses... I mean, if command had
let that case go fonnard. We were on it.
- Look at that. It's the dove.
- Oh, right.
Look at that.
- So what do you think?
- What do I think?
I think you're gonna take
the sergeant's exam next month.
And because I have Andy krawczyk's ear
and because he has city hall's ear,
you're gonna make sergeant.
Then you'll come out here to the southeast
where, because I'm your father-in-law,
you're gonna be assigned a daytime shift
in a quiet sector.
Then you'll take the lieutenant's exam
where you'll also score high.
I don't want to make rank,
I want to work cases. Good cases.
Roland...
Listen to me.
You did good with the drug thing.
You buckled down, you did the work.
Except for that thing with the grand jury,
you took some of the stink off yourself.
If you'll just shut up and listen to me,
you might actually have a career
in this department.
- This radio ain't working that well.
- You're losing it.
- You're losing the station.
- What you mean?
We're so far from Baltimore,
we're losing the station.
- Try a Philly station or some shit like that.
- Philly radio is different?
You fucking with me? You never heard
a station outside of Baltimore?
I ain't never left Baltimore
except that boys' village shit for one day.
I didn't hear no radio up in that bitch.
Come on, man. You're killing me. Stop.
It's been perfect tomato weather.
These wonderful hot, humid days
and then rain at night...
- This a Philly station?
- How the fuck would I know?
Why would anybody wanna leave Baltimore?
That's what I'm asking.
Yo, that be the exit. Take that shit.
- So far, they on it.
- Mm-hm.
Ahoy, Matey!
The girls always told me about the little
man in the boat. Now I know who they meant.
- Come on board, man, I wanna show you.
- Uh-uh, fuck, no.
- What's the matter?
- The bunk can't swim.
- I ain't too good at floating neither.
- So what brings you to the water's edge?
Ilene Nathan called.
Gant case is coming up in four weeks.
She wants to do preliminaries
on our witnesses.
That means the old lady from the projects,
which is no problem,
and your man Omar, who's in the wind.
Uh-huh.
- You got a line on Omar, Jimmy?
- Well, he's not to starboard.
- That's port, fool.
- How the fuck would you know?
Come on, let me buy you lunch
and we can think on this shit together.
If I leave, I gotta tell my sergeant.
That reminds me, landsman wants his $10.
- What for?
- For betting that you'd ride the boat.
Tell that fucker he won't see that money. He
probably told rawls where I didn't wanna go.
Jimmy, ain't the same
there without your ass.
Better, actually. Hey, come on, now.
The canal gets dredged, we all work.
Your people, my people.
The canal's the key, nat.
Yeah. You know how much money you'd
spend to even get them talking about that?
If we don't take a shot,
we might as well roll over and die.
No, you get them to rebuild the grain pier.
You got a hundred ships right there.
The best you'll do is one or two
extra gangs a week on them blowers.
That's six or seven-man gangs at best.
Yeah, but you try for that,
you might come away with something.
You go down to Annapolis
asking for the goddamn canal,
you'll come back
with your shrivelled-ass dick in your hand.
What's more,
if the grain pier don't get fixed up soon,
some asshole's gonna fuck us
by building condominiums.
- Nat, if the canal were two feet deeper...
- Fuck the canal.
I'm gonna go to the district council. I'm
gonna tell them to push for the grain pier.
- You feel me?
- Nat, calm the fuck down.
Goddamn checkers local - always acting like
you're the king of everything and shit.
Nat, listen to me. If we...
Y'all need to crawl
back down in them holds.
Remind yourself of who you is
and where you come from.
Damn, frank.
We just sat here and watched nat coxson
take a shit all over you.
And shrivel-dick motherfucker that you are,
you take it.
I wake up every morning
with an angry, blue-veined diamond-cutter.
I was gonna enlighten the president of the
local 47 on this point. He chose to depart.
- Blue steel, gentlemen.
- For Christ's sake!
Three and a half inches of hard blue steel!
- Nicky boy, you working today?
- As a lasher for big Roy's crew.
Attaboy. Make the family proud.
First day they give me in two weeks.
- Is ott around?
- On his ass, as usual.
Worthless fuck owes me 20
for them lotto tickets.
Hey, Nick.
Need to see the Greek and get a number.
He's got one on the way.
- Today?
- Tomorrow.
The Atlantic light over at north point.
All right.
- Yo, frank.
- What's up?
You gotta get with Ziggy, man.
He's all over the place.
I'm here since eight.
You know I been here since eight.
- Hold your horses.
- You fucking goose!
I'm gonna find it for you.
Just shut the fuck up.
- How we doing?
- Ain't a problem, chief.
Fuck it ain't. I'm here since eight
for crane-to-chassis
and tweety bird here lost the can.
It ain't lost.
It's right here on the manifest
as a hot box. Where is it, zig?
- It's either in bay 7 or...
- Bay 7 is empty, man.
Or in 8. In that case...
It's definitely somewheres in the stacks.
- Jesus fucking Christ.
- You're killing me, Ziggy, fucking killing me.
Get me a number for your shipping agent.
I'll call and try to square it. And you...
Clock out today and leave your box.
Don't come the fuck back.
You hear me, zig? You're fired.
Later for you, goofus.
Fucking guy.
He loses his job and he couldn't care less.
- He ain't fired, man.
- No?
That's his father.
- How fast do you need this?
- Trial's in a month.
Got to start prepping it this week.
Officer burns...
Detective.
I heard they posted you down here, but...
I mean, you know, damn.
- These motherfuckers don't play, do they?
- So what brings you downstairs?
I was pulling evidence on the gant case.
Trial date for bird is next month
and ilene Nathan wanted to be ready.
You give him my love.
- Who?
- Bird
- No evidence.
- What do you mean?
Submission slip says, "row bb, section 14,
shelf 3, four, right rear." It says that.
- So?
- No such thing.
Bb has 12 sections. This says 14.
You see what I'm saying? No evidence.
Winters kill off
the weaker varieties of caterpillars...
- Fuckin'...
- That's of an entirely different breed...
Fuck.
It's not a protection against
caterpillars, they eat right through it,
but it is a sort of warning system.
They here.
Franus, you made it.
Hey, father, got you covered here.
Come on.
Do you wanna see your window?
Only franus sobotka would send
all the way to esslingen for stained glass.
The Germans are hard-headed,
but you can't beat them for craft.
I was glad to do it, father,
for the church, you know.
- I need to ask you something in return.
- Anything I can do.
- I need some face time with the senator.
- Barbara?
She comes to the early mass on Sunday,
the one in Polish.
We got problems. We need to see
something happen with the c&d canal.
The granary pier's been down for a year.
I got tough guys coming in
to confess things I never heard before.
I don't need you to tell me
how bad things are at the docks.
You'll set something up with mikulski soon?
You didn't need a German window
to ask me for that, Francis.
What's more, you've made offerings
way above what it would take
to get that window up there.
How long since your last confession?
I'll see you, father.
- The shit might be somewhere else, man.
- Yo, the shit always up in the door, man.
Motherfucker, you've been watching us.
You see any shit come up out of there?
- You seen we ain't take shit up off this car.
- Yeah, yeah.
Who gonna believe us? The shit is missing.
And fuck what you're saying.
- All he'll hear is this shit is fucking missing.
- Check it again.
The shit ain't there, man.
Call your man and say so.
Nigger, what you say?
- I said, check it again, goddamn it!
- Whoa, chill, chill.
Yo, man, out that shit the fuck out.
Fuck. What the fuck is going on today, man?
Taking their time, ain't they?
What the hell is going on?
- Come on, man.
- Damn!
- Ain't anywhere in this section either.
- Start on the next row.
Lieutenant, those two bags
could be anywhere in this basement.
You're right.
- We could be here all night.
- Right again.
So that's overtime, right?
Fuck me. I still cannot type.
- Fucking white boys, I fucking love 'em.
- Yeah?
- Dumb as a box of rocks.
- Who?
White boys.
The braindeads in my Kane street case.
I call and tell him iwanna buy drugs.
You know what he says?
"Ok, I'll sell you drugs.
How much drugs do you want?"
I swear to god, kima, they don't code it,
they don't ask for a meet, nothing.
Then when you make the deal,
there's no bullshit.
It's the guy himself saying, "I brought
the drugs. Did you bring the money?"
I have much respect for black people after
working with these idiots for two weeks.
For white boys to sell drugs here, they have
to make different laws, even it out for them.
- Affirmative action.
- Leave no white man behind.
- Herc, what the fuck do you want?
- I need you to do the seizures.
You got titles, deeds, registrations?
- What do you have?
- You do that. You're the forfeiture unit.
I write the affidavits and the filing
for the city solicitor.
You've gotta give me the information
on what we're taking.
- That's a fucking hassle.
- You want the property, do the papennork.
You gotta step up, herc. You don't
have me or carver to lean on here.
No? Come on the raids tomorrow. Take
a few doors with me for old times' sake.
- You taking doors?
- Two houses and a bar on Kane street.
Come on, kima, mount up with us.
I know you miss it.
I'm done rolling round the gutter.
I am inside now.
- You're a house cat now, huh?
- I made a promise.
I gotta say, kima, if you were a guy -
and, in some ways,
you're better than most guys -
your friends would buy you a beer
and let you know.
- Let me know what?
- You're fucking whipped.
- Whipped?
- Pussy-whipped within an inch of your life.
I kid you not.
So where we find Omar?
Who?
- He say anything else?
- No. Just to come back.
All of us.
- How he say it?
- You know, hejust said it.
Fuck.
Yeah.
Shit.
- They holding to it?
- So far.
All right.
They got the times right?
How about the mileage?
All right.
So I'm gonna ask you one more time.
- You never saw him out the car?
- No.
- You stayed with him the whole time?
- Every minute.
How long
before he came out the parking garage?
- How long was he on his own?
- Not enough time to do shit, string.
- He was in and out, like, three minutes.
- Chill.
This shit is fucked up.
You follow directions?
- I did...
- Wrote down the mileage?
- Yeah.
- Let me see.
See, right there.
Mmm.
No, you three-tenths of a mile long, dawg,
and if you followed directions,
you wouldn't be.
Yo, string, I did everything
like I should, man. I swear.
You got answers?
You didn't take a detour in Camden when
they shut down blocks on the boulevard?
- You hurt your foot.
- My foot?
The way you kicked that tire Jack
the way you did.
- You was on us the whole time?
- Who, me?
Y'all had people following us?
So where it at?
Ok. Hey, you know,
you should take me with you.
I should meet these guys. If I Meet them,
we can figure out ways to do business.
- Zig, these guys are real.
- What, I ain't real?
Six degrees. Everybody's going home
to Sauerkraut and santy claus
and here comes a gang of us
walking the other way...
Little big Roy with his wooden leg.
- Christ, them wooden shovels!
- Yeah.
You children know nothing
about them wooden shovels.
Can't have no sparks, working grain!
- Kaboom!
- It's more like kaput.
Never gonna see another grain ship
in Baltimore.
- No...
- Zig, you believe these fucking dinosaurs?
They sit around talking shit about
how they used to off-load with shovels.
- Carry fucking railroad cars on their backs!
- And drink whiskey through a fire hose!
And go home and fuck their wives silly.
Fucking heroes back then!
The shit is thick in here tonight.
What can you do?
This generation just don't know.
- Ain't never gonna be what it was.
- No.
Every night with these old fucks
is like 1952 and shit.
Hey, boys, you know, when I was your age,
I unloaded ten ships a goddamn day!
Stick it to 'em, zig!
I had do it with one arm after a
300-pound bag of Polish dildos fell on me!
- What the fuck is a Polish dildo?
- Actually, at my house, it's a ring of kielbasa.
Hey, hey. But where you boys hail from,
I'm sure any old breakfast link will do!
- You know he's gonna pull out his dick.
- That boy ain't right.
It was just me and my old wooden leg
and my old wooden shovel
and my glass eye and my Polish pencil.
Like anyone from the checkers local
ever used anything but a real pencil.
Shit, they don't push one of them no more!
Talking trash about 1514.
Jesus h Christ, you know what?
All hands starboard!
The old tub is listing. Can you feel her?
You wanna know why?
Cause them old fucks
done unloaded so much bullshit
that this whole motherfucker's
gonna capsize!
Brace yourselves, we're sinking!
Goddamn it, Ziggy, you're not
taking your dick out in here again.
Let me show you old gents some bulk cargo
that none of yous could ever handle.
Who says they don't make them like
they used to? Pretty boy is on the town!
Fucking Ziggy, man.
- Bring her in the boat?
- Hell, no.
- She'll fall apart if we try to bring her in.
- What's the plan, then?
We'll hook her real good.
We'll tow her slowly over to the pier.
- What's she look like?
- What do you mean?
- How long you think she's been in?
- She's fresh.
- Legs are broke, though.
- Probably a jumper from the bridge.
All right, ma. Shit.
Yo, zig.
Ziggy.
Kitchen's closed.
No service for drunks
who can't get up in time to catch a ship.
- What ship?
- Your father says the talco line is in today.
That makes two ships at north point.
It's the Atlantic light.
Ain't due until this afternoon.
That still is no excuse.
Good morning, mom.
Couple of goddamn drunks I got.
Don't leave
without taking your cousin with you.
I gotta clean in there
and I ain't gonna do it around his carcass.
Well, you keep us
guessing, don't you, Stan?
At Sunday mass, you can't be found. Early
on a Tuesday, you arrive with an army?
2,500 from myself and every other polack
in three districts and four firehouses.
- And to what do we owe such generosity?
- A surprise.
We ordered up a window for where
you renovated the nave. A memorial.
To Polish police and firefighters.
Found this craftsman down in Glen burnie
that you would not believe.
- For the nave?
- Yeah, for the nave.
We could use another window
on the second floor of the rectory.
- The rectory?
- The upstairs hallway.
How much did them dock boys offer
for this spot? I can match it.
Offerings are confidential, Stan.
- And as you can see...
- I can go as high as 4,000.
Tell me if they went higher than four.
More than four. From the docks.
How the hell...
I'm sorry, father.
- Who came to you with the offer?
- Francis sobotka.
- Frank has that kind of money?
- It was from his local.
The checkers? They don't
have a hundred guys left paying dues.
It's a parish of givers, Stan.
Maybe you talk to frank.
Work it out somehow.
Yeah, we'll talk.
Major?
- Well, well, if it isn't barnacle bill, the sailor.
- Hey, ray, how you been?
I got nothing but red ink under my name.
Landsman's become an asshole with teeth.
- Fish your wish, huh?
- Jumper, probably.
- This close to the bridge.
- Probably, yeah.
- Pretty, though.
- She is.
I go in the men's room this morning.
Guess who's puking his guts out.
- Bunk moreland.
- How'd you know?
Useless fuck can't hold his liquor.
- What's happenin', man?
- What's up, fam?
- You ain't heard from Roberto?
- Not a goddamn word.
Billy still got our money though, right?
So you need to get down to New York, man.
Fuck kind of game this nigger playing?
You sure of our people?
I broke down their stories
and they were clean.
Besides, I had some good people watch 'em.
- Who?
- Tank, country.
- How long he been home?
- A month. Still on parole.
- He said fuck that, straight back in the mix.
- All right.
So good, it ain't on us, it's on Roberto.
Set it straight, know what I mean?
When you go hard on them, take it light,
but be firm.
They got our money
and we ain't got the product.
You feel me? This shit ain't right.
How you fixed in here othennise, b?
This ain't no thing, man, know what I mean?
You come in here, you get your mind right.
You do two days. It's the day
you come in this motherfucker...
- And the day you get out this motherfucker.
- That's right.
Exactly.
- What's up? Coming from the hiring hall?
- Yeah, I'm working the Atlantic light today.
- How's it looking for local 47?
- Outta luck.
Ro/ros isn't going
to anybody lower than a g-series.
Best you can get - half a day doing break-bulk
on an aluminum load at locust point.
- Half a day, huh?
- Seniority sucks.
- Yeah, if you ain't senior, it does.
- You got that right.
- I'm outta here.
- See you.
- The fuck you ain't wake me up for?
- Just got up, fuck-face?
No, your ma makes a good breakfast.
- No fucking way.
- Bacon and eggs, baby.
- You going down to see the Greek, right?
- Ziggy...
Come on, man.
I ain't gonna fuck it up for you.
For Christ's sake, will you just
get in the car already? Come on, let's go.
Swear to god, Ziggy,
you open your mouth, I'll fucking kill you.
- Nicky from the docks.
- Spiros.
How are you?
- Who's your friend?
- Zig, my uncle's kid.
- Your uncle?
- Frankie, yeah.
Ziggy's his oldest.
My car broke down, you know. He drove.
So you must be the Greek.
Well, I'm Greek, anyway.
Hey, Boris badanoff,
I know you from around the way, right?
Why am I Boris? I don't understand this.
Everywhere I am Boris.
- Shit, you're Russian, right?
- No, Ukraine. Kiev is Ukraine.
- It's the same difference.
- No, you're wrong.
What's the matter?
You don't like being called Boris?
- Sergei.
- No way!
Boris is way better. It's like the guy
from the cartoon. Boris and Natasha?
Bullwinkle, man. Rocky and bullwinkle?
- You want some coffee, pie?
- No, I'm good.
- Actually, what kind of pie you got?
- Hey, zig, shut the fuck up, huh?
Sorry.
Who's that guy?
No, it's cool. He's cool.
- That's frank's kid, huh?
- Yeah.
He's in the union, you know, but he's, like,
an I-series so he ain't getting any hours.
- Same deal, same rate.
- All right. Who's driving?
Again?
You don't wanna mix it up a little more? Make
it so customs doesn't put no names to faces.
When you trust a man, you stay with him.
- Ok.
- All right.
- Boris it is.
- Sergei.
Yeah, whatever. Come
on, fuck-nuts. Let's go.
- How's the open-face Turkey?
- It's shit. Let's go.
See you guys later.
Bullwinkle?
Polacks.
You fucking embarrassed me in there, man.
You embarrassed yourself, zig.
You seen my nephew anywhere?
Nick? Not yet. I don't
think he got any hours.
- Hey, frank.
- Hey, darling.
Just so I can finish my papennork early,
what are your people gonna steal today?
I don't know. Couple luxury sedans,
some color tvs, widescreen.
Couple of cans of vodka,
maybe a whole container ship.
Okey-dokey. Y'all have a good one.
You let her fuck with you like that?
She's all right. I like her.
I checked the computer. It's bay
9, cell 11. It's right on the bottom.
- You working the light, ain't you?
- I'm on it.
- Did they say anything else?
- No. Just that it's the same money to us.
Let's go.
All right, uncle frank.
- Winona.
- Jimmy, where you been?
Look who it is - sailor
boy. You owe me ten.
Fuck you. You told rawls where
I didn't wanna go. You made it happen, Jay.
- I told him where you didn't wanna go.
- And they sent me there.
I knew rawls was pissed, I didn't know
how pissed. What can I tell you?
- Where's bunk?
- Out on a call with crutchfield.
That girl, she come off the bridge or what?
Doc Frazier posted her.
Blunt-force trauma to the head and chest.
- Dead before she hits the water.
- What about the defense wounds?
Bruising on three fingers.
We saw that when we picked her up.
- You missed the defense wounds?
- I wasn't looking.
- Thought she went off the bridge.
- She has no coat or shoes on.
Maybe they came off
in the water, maybe not.
I don't see her going to the bridge in winter
dressed like she was, but that's just me.
Tell bunk I was here, will you? Have fun.
We already had our fun.
Dumping her on Baltimore county.
On the county?
You fished her out east of the bridge.
Baltimore county. She's their stat.
- You sold them on that?
- Rawls did.
He called up the colonel, said, "you
got one hell of a murder on your hands."
It's all about self-preservation, Jimmy.
That's something you never learned.
Hey, Norris. State police, line 2.
A little to the right.
Good, good, bring her down.
It's there whenever they want it.
Now that you are my client, Mr. Bell, we are
protected by the attorney-client privilege.
- I thought Roberto would be here.
- Not likely.
This, I'm afraid, was in Monday's papers.
It seems Roberto castellano y silva
has been targeted by the DEA.
That's why we didn't do the business?
Roberto and his people aren't going
to be getting involved in anything
that could complicate the situation.
Usually when you take a fail, you get back
in there cause you know nobody's watching.
Sometimes. And sometimes you wonder
how it is you got caught in the first place
and you decide to change the pattern.
- He took our money.
- Your payment arrived as our problem did.
I'm told the money
is on the way back to Baltimore.
You know, I get the feeling that you're
blaming us for Roberto's... predicament.
Perhaps your problems in Baltimore and
my client's problems here are coincidental.
- But right now...
- Listen to me.
He was the first to
know that we took a hit.
He knows no one came close to rolling over
us and all the documents from the case.
Nonetheless, we have a legitimate concern.
Considering the scope
of Mr. Barksdale's operation,
his sentence was, to say the least, mild.
But if the possibility
exists, however unlikely,
that the leniency he received
was the result of cooperation...
Well, you understand
our position, I'm sure.
Frank, it's sitting out there and this
Russian fuck won't take it off the pier.
I ain't blind.
I don't like it sitting out
in the open that long.
The customs seal is broke. Somebody'll
see it. Our asses are hanging out here.
- Yeah?
- Nicky, what the fuck? It's still here.
- Shit.
- Yeah.
- Where's Sergei?
- Parked at the end of the lot.
- What's he waiting for?
- No fucking idea.
The ship's almost empty.
They need to shit or get off the pot.
- I'll look into it.
- Yeah.
Ok, I understand.
Fuck it. Get it on a fifth wheel
and lose it in the stack. We're at risk.
- Hey.
I ain't lying when I say
this papennork is kicking my ass.
Maybe so,
but you come through the door in one piece.
You like to think so, but all these
paper cuts are starting to take their toll.
Aw, you big, nasty detective. Come here.
Let me give your little boo-boo a kiss!
- All this?
- I'm just getting started.
$1,000 for the doctor.
$1,000 each time, girlfriend.
Every month till I'm pregnant.
- There's gotta be a better way.
- That would be on you, sweetheart.
Come up with a suitable donor
and we pay a lot less.
Not with your pussy
would I fuck any of these guys.
What did you just say?
You didn't just say that!
Sergeant.
Your floater's come back. County boys
are putting her on our side of the bridge.
- No fucking way.
- Yeah.
Some useless fuck in our marine unit faxed
them a report on tides and wind currents.
Shows the body went in the water
west of the bridge and drifted out.
Mcnulty.
Fucking Jimmy.
Fucking with us for the fun of it.
I gotta give the son of a bitch some credit
for wit on this one.
- Cocksucker.
- Motherfucker.
The count is right. What's on the shelf?
Mace carrying ten down here,
moe man holding about 38 up top.
I checked the stash, yo, and we way low.
- Moe man taking our shit.
- What he holding?
He said about 30-something, but I know
that ain't right. I'm gonna fuck him up.
First thing you think to
do is fuck a nigger up.
When your brick brain gonna realize there's
more to this here than thumpin' on niggers?
- What moe supposed to be holding?
- 38, thereabout.
- Ain't you the damn fool?
- But then we low.
If we low, it's cause
string want us that way.
When he want us up, we'll be up.
Stringer's on top of this shit.
He on top of everything.
Go back to your spot, man.
Fucking mcnulty.
The prince of tides.
Brother, you feeling strong today? See
if you can get his ass out of that chair.
He said it was fine if
you want to hit him, too.
Hey, hey, hey. What's the first thing a guy
from local 47 does after he gets laid?
- What?
- Wipes the pepper spray from his eyes!
Hey, frank, something's going on.
Come on.
- It's fucking girls, man. Young ones.
- A dozen of them.
Dead? They're dead?
English sdh