- Got that wmd here.
- No. I want what you had the other day.
- This shit here?
- You was calling it bin laden.
But now it's wmd.
It will mass destruct your ass.
So this the hi-test?
Same shit, new name. You be all right.
Bang-bang-bang. Bang-bang-bang.
Ok, get dressed. I pressed you
some clothes and laid them out.
And don't forget that book bag neither.
You got your chrome, young 'UN?
I'll take mine.
Y'all mind the crossfire, hear? Let's go.
- They coming up the alley!
- They coming back!
Aim for the chest, brother.
Yo. Slide up.
Get down on that floor and stay there.
- You hear me, boy?
- Ok, mama.
- Come on!
- Fuck!
Shit!
- Why you running?
- What the fuck?
Oh, shit!
Hit that nigger!
- Bitches!
- Get down!
- Stay on it!
- Shit!
Bitches!
That's right, come out.
Why you hiding?
- What's happening?
- Come on!
- Move out, yo!
- Yaaah!
Drama done with, boy.
You gotta get yourself to school.
Get in, damn it!
Tt, you hear me?
Come on now. The drama's done.
Get your bags and get yourself to school.
I told you, you gotta get ready...
No!
When you walk through the garden
you gotta watch your back
well, I beg your pardon
walk the straight and narrow track
if you walk with Jesus
he's gonna save your soul
you gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
he's got the fire and the fury
at his command
well, you don't have to worry
if you hold onto Jesus' hand
we'll all be safe from Satan
when the thunder rolls
we just gotta keep the devil
way down in the hole
Down in the hole
down in the hole
you gotta help me keep the devil
They're changing up?
Looking for my la-z-boys.
Five you got for me, right?
- That shipment is tomorrow.
- Got it.
That's what the warehouse was giving us.
Straight to the point drug talk.
No muss, no fuss. Now listen.
Pyramid incorporated.
May I help you?
- You got them davinas or what?
- We no longer carry that line, sir.
Between us, we been sitting
on that warehouse every minute
since that truck came off the docks.
No players coming or going.
No drug-related traffic.
To top it off, sobotka
hasn't used his cellphone since.
- We tipped our hand.
- That second can.
The port police
making a traffic stop spooked them.
Then we fucked ourselves over nothing.
They dumped that can as a misdelivery.
- What?
- They probably changed that up, too.
If they think we're onto them,
they switch the can just to be safe.
And it goes offjust to
see if we pull them up.
Which we did... which I did.
No, they're not on us completely.
If they were, they'd be
shutting down and rolling out.
Instead, they're just sitting inside,
turning away calls,
waiting us out.
I, for one, am a patient motherfucker.
Don't waste film.
I been here so fucking long
that you're starting to look good to me.
Anything?
The drugs go in, they gotta come out.
I mean, what the fuck?
Little late. Used to be, when
a nine-year-old hit the pavement,
a district commander
would be there in minutes.
We're living in a brave new world.
- I was in Washington with burrell.
- DC? What for?
Burrell took some district commanders
down to DOJ.
Pimping ourselves for Grant money.
So what do we got?
Nine-year-old catches
a stray through the window.
- Dead?
- Pronounced at university.
- Witnesses?
- No names.
Two crews arguing over the real estate.
We got casings from
three different calibers.
Your people in tactical should hit
the area drug corners and collect bodies.
- Fucking pointless.
- We get enough shitbirds, this case can fall.
I ain't talking about that.
I'm talking about this whole mess.
Been chasing this shit from one corner
to the next like it's a plan.
Hit the corners, Howard. Take scalps.
You'll feel better when you do.
You told us about worldcom
and the name change-up. You said...
I said change the name. I didn't say
nothing about taking people off a corner.
We changed the name so many times
that don't nobody come down no more.
And them carrollton boys had it going on.
- Who shot the young 'UN?
- I don't know.
I don't think it was us.
Them other niggers was going wild...
The cops are gonna
have to bang some heads on this one.
They got to. That means we gotta
shut everything down until this shit pass.
The towers, the low-rises. Everything
gotta take a long fucking time-out!
I know, string.
I'm sorry, man.
Let me tell you something, man.
This here game, it's more than
the rep you carry, the corner you hold.
You gotta be fierce, I know that.
But more than that,
you gotta show some flex.
Give and take on both sides.
- You hear me?
- Yeah.
Ok, anything that fired a bullet
out on that corner has gotta disappear.
Not the storm drains.
Call that nigger shamrock and drive
all that chrome over to the harbor.
All right.
Coming up, yo.
I got people waiting on a package, but Sergei
says until we're sure about the police...
We're not going to be doing
that business for a few days.
Your uncle, he is right to be careful.
But, Niko, if you are
going to be doing this,
- you should not be talking to us about it.
- Why not?
We are more, what you call wholesalers.
I'm kind of small-time, huh?
You are not so big, but
you're among friends.
Call that number.
- Talk to him.
- Mike?
- This white Mike?
- You know him?
From Curtis bay. Iwent
to southern high school with the guy.
You are with us now,
so he will be fair. No problem.
The rest of our business...
We will disappear these containers.
All of them clean.
Take them to newkirk street.
If there is a problem,
they will stop the trucks
or we will see the police.
If not, no more worries.
All right.
We are off the warehouse phone now?
I've given the new number to our people.
This is bullshit. If they were onto
the truck, they would've searched it.
Five-o!
Hey! Where you guys going?
Come on, you know the deal.
Get the fuck up against the wall! Hurry up.
Come on, keep moving.
Get him. Down.
This is bullshit, man.
You know I ain't did nothing.
Everybody gets the special downtown.
One baloney sandwich and one white milk.
- Just shut the fuck up.
- Man, I'm clean, you hear me?
- What are you doing in the pit?
- Saying no to drugs.
Don't just say no to drugs, motherfucker.
Say, "no, thank you."
Put your fucking head down,
step up and get in.
Sit down, stupid. Watch your head going in.
Slide over, asshole.
Shame a kid had to get killed
before we got around to doing this.
What exactly is it that we're doing?
Young boy killed over bullshit.
Now you got the police
crawling all the way up your ass.
It's a good day to be an eastside nigger,
I gotta say.
Thing is, it ain't gonna happen like that
if I take you up on your offer.
I'll be out there selling that real.
My boys ain't gonna be scuffling.
They ain't gonna be standing on
nobody else's corner, starting no shit.
You westside. You must've heard
of Charlie sollers, right?
- No.
- Goes back to Franklin and fremont.
- All the way back to the '60s and shit.
- Sollers?
Sold heroin like it was water.
The motherfucker made some money.
I don't know who the
fuck you talking about.
I know you don't. And the police don't.
And the stick-up boys
wouldn't have a fucking clue.
Cause Charlie sollers just sold dope.
No profile, no street rep.
Just buy for a dollar, sell for two.
Sometimes, when your back up
against the wall, you go to the gun.
I know. I been there.
But you ain't gotta live by it.
Avon...
Avon a soldier.
That's who you want with you when
the shit fly. But as far as business go...
- You still got that connect?
- Right off the boat, string.
All right. I'm gonna buy from you
at the price you paying...
And I'll let you walk
that shit in the towers.
You can have 734, 770 and 221.
I keep the other three.
How you gonna tell it to avon?
It makes sense, don't it?
He gonna hear something
when it makes sense.
Right?
No shit.
- I thought you was in with Nicky.
- Fuck Nick.
Said you was his other half.
I don't want his fucking money.
That's drug money. Drugs are bad.
Consider what that shit does
to the community.
You spent all last year with
white Mike. Remember?
A man can grow.
Besides, I got a caper that is gonna put
that horseshit to shame. I'm telling you.
You want in?
- What do I gotta do?
- What a longshoreman does best.
- Your duck won't touch pikesville rye.
- He drinks mid-shelf.
He don't like that rail shit.
Fuck if I wouldn't give my right leg
for a shot and a beer.
- New Charles in the house.
- Moving pretty good.
- I'm waiting on a prosthetic.
- You got a lawyer?
Nat coxson hooked me up through the union.
What's with the duck?
- Hey, zig.
- Charlie.
- You gotta let go of your name.
- Say what?
Yeah, new Charles don't work
for a one-legged fuck.
Yeah, maybe "stump".
- You know what? "Peg".
- "New Peggy".
- How about "tilt"?
- Tilt?
Tilt. Just like a pinball machine.
Tilt. I like that.
Tilt.
I called a couple of nights ago.
Told you I might be in town.
- So, this is your first time?
- Yep, first time for me.
What do you do, Jimmy? Are you the police?
Do you work with the police?
No. Christ, no.
No, I'm a traveling salesman.
I travel and, you know...
- Where do you live?
- I'm not gonna tell you that.
- I live out of town.
- I don't think we can help you tonight.
Thank you.
You sucked. I mean, really.
Fuck if I thought I was gonna be interrogated.
I'm just looking to get laid, right?
Hey, fucknuts.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
Christ, Ziggy. What the... zig...
Jesus, zig. What the fuck?
- What's up with my cousin?
- Don't talk to me about that asshole.
- Drank himself to death.
- Oh, shit.
What kind of fool
would give a duck whiskey?
That boy ain't right.
His fucking bird couldn't
hold liquor for shit.
- La-z-boys?
- And davinas. Male and female.
- Dope and coke.
- What's a Davina?
- It's like a love seat.
- Any line on weight?
- All whole numbers.
- No halves, quarters, eight-balls?
- Ounces?
- What numbers they putting on the furniture?
Nothing much above five.
Proposition Joe has Ashland all the way
up to north. Ten corners.
Five ounces wouldn't last him past lunch.
It's kilos. We're on the main stem.
What was coming and going last night?
Not much. No trucks
in, some cars in and out,
but none of the drug players we saw before.
Whatever was in that last truckload
probably went out in car trunks.
They're doing their distribution
somewhere else.
Job one is to get back to a good phone.
The PC that got you the warehouse
phone will get you anywhere else.
- All we need is the new number.
- Any newlines in there?
- The phone people say no.
- Probably going to a cellphone.
Best bet is to get the new number
of the Russian's cellphone.
Ok, then. Freamon and Prez,
stay on one shift in the wiretap room.
Bunk and Russell, man the other.
Herc and carver are on newkirk street
to see if the warehouse traffic picks up.
Mcnulty and greggs
have the prostitution ring,
but the people handling the girls
have been cautious about fresh Johns,
so we're gonna need a new angle there.
Questions?
- What was your play with those girls?
- Out-of-town salesman.
- How far out of town?
- What do you mean?
The further out of town,
the more they believe.
You do any accents?
English, Scottish, something like that?
Crikey!
I was looking to get a little hanky-panky
and this bloke gave me this number
to call when I got across the pond.
Work on it, son. Work on it.
200,000? That isn't a quarter
of what they owe.
They will pay another two
once their shipment clears the docks.
- And then?
- That is all.
These Colombians are without honor,
spiros. They are cheats.
- The chemicals we sent are good, no?
- No complaint. They want more, even.
And they understand we can guarantee
their product clears customs?
- Mm-hm.
- Huh?
- And still, they try to chisel.
- Why? What are they thinking?
That it is all profit for us.
That we will settle for half
because 400,000 is still a lot of money.
The Greek will be angry.
This is business, eton.
The Greek? He will be smart.
- Got a charge?
- We ain't got no charge, asshole.
Now shut the fuck up.
- I didn't do shit.
- Jesus.
You accidentally shoot one nine-year-old
in his bedroom
and the city gets its undies in a bunch.
To err is human, I say.
The mayor went to the scene last night.
Said the crime will not stand.
- Tell him we got no eyeball witness.
- How about the street talk?
Mentions of a 17-year-old, bodie.
Narcotics has him as Preston broadus.
Why is young Preston not being hurled
around one of our interrogation rooms?
We got cars on his grandma's as we speak.
What the fuck you think
you're dealing with here? Amateurs?
Fuck Nick. This is my thing.
You want in, you gotta deal with me.
I got s-class and sl-class benzes,
roadsters, sedans, cabriolets.
Brand-new, keys in the ignition,
nothing stripped.
- Off the docks?
- No shit, off the docks.
Do I look like a fucking car dealer?
Twenty on the dollar.
But if we're gonna do this,
I need you to order a minimum of three,
or it ain't worth it for me.
Now, base price on an s430 starts at 73.
You round it,
I get 15 for each car that you want.
A stolen car is a stolen car. Without
title, who is going to pay even ten for it?
In Baltimore, maybe.
But where you're from...
I bet you got family
that don't give two fucks
whether or not an American car
got a title on it.
It would be a sad state of affairs
if an international entrepreneur like you
didn't know what to do
with a couple of extra Mercedes.
Big night for Jimmy mcnulty.
Or should I say James cromwell
of knightsbridge, stepney and mersey.
Excuse me?
Cromwell was the English fuck
who stole my ancestors' land
and the others
are all from rock and roll songs.
Ten tomorrow night, the shuttle comes for
me on the parking lot off Russell street.
Good work.
We'll get greggs to wire you up.
Shame we're not up on a good phone.
Be nice to tickle the wire
when we raid the brothel.
A little luck,
maybe we get back up before then.
One other thing.
I'm kind of bothered
that a Russian immigrant this deep in dirt
doesn't have anything on the computer.
You still got that friend in woodlawn? I'd
like to know what the FBI has in its database.
After that meeting on the barksdale case,
I made a point of pissing him off.
So what? You do that to everybody.
George glekas. He owns the appliance
store where that second can landed.
Run his ass, too.
Cut another guy in
and run them out the bobtail Lane.
These babies start disappearing
and everybody in the terminal
is gonna suspect an inside job.
We need bolt cutters for the fence
and then enough wood beams to make
a track across the grass onto the road.
Why bother? We can run them cars
over that patch of grass.
That ain't the plan.
- I just saw a can disappear.
- Talco line?
- Pakusa working it?
- It's him.
- Do we try to follow?
- We know where it's going.
- 12-08, you copy?
- 12-08. What's up?
We got a can that might
be coming to you off the port.
Can number Paul-Mike-Quebec-Victor...
4-0-0-7-6-5, check digit two.
- What do you want us to do with it?
- See if it arrives.
- And if it does?
- See what happens then.
You wanna know something, carv?
I'm starting to think that, as criminal
investigators, we're not really respected.
That ain't necessary, Jimmy.
I knew we were fucking the dog
on that barksdale thing. Who do I tell?
We got this new asac,
thinks it's all about loyalty and ass-kiss.
It ain't like your agency. You piss
them off, you ride the boat. Here...
Well, you find yourself assigned to some
fucking dustbowl Indian res in Arkansas.
- I was out of line, Fitz.
- Fuck it. What you got there?
White boys. A different look for you.
They're all showing clean.
What's the chance of that?
Ncic and naddis are a dead end.
Customs had a little intel
on this guy, glekas.
- Customs has intel on him?
- Mm-hm.
Should show here.
Let me try something else with it.
This'll give us any contact
he might have had with us.
- Something out of San Diego.
- On glekas?
Let's see.
I call hyattsville, I need three
forms and a lieutenant's approval.
Agent Ernest koutris, please.
Believe me, we ain't short on papennork
here either. Agent koutris?
Not much to it. We pulled his chain in
a stolen goods case I worked in '95, '96.
He was just crumbs, so no charges.
But I did an interview.
The guy struck me
as just a mope playing it slick.
Yeah, I can send you what I got.
All right. If you need it, let me know.
We need to talk.
Anyone following?
Run up and down the street.
Take tag numbers from cars.
- All week I've done it. Nothing.
- Again.
The truck is here.
Lester, it's here.
- They off-load anything?
- Not yet.
Ok, wait on it.
See, the thing about it, Preston,
is that you're unbelievably stupid.
I don't say it to upset you.
Just to state a fact.
He doesn't think so.
Nobody ever thinks they're stupid.
It's part of the stupidity.
You don't need to tell us what happened.
We know.
We got you, we got your guns,
we got the whole fucking story.
Where that lawyer at, man?
You just fucked up. Way you looked
at the bag, you know what's in there.
That's you, right there, fucking up.
- I don't know what you talking about.
- You fucked up.
We even got your prints
on one of the guns. We even got that.
Which one?
That's you right there.
Lawyer.
They were asking about me?
San Diego.
San Diego was a long time ago.
Our friend in Washington
does not know why. Only that they asked.
You told me the police
looking into the women were local.
They were. No FBI.
- We've been running clean containers?
- Yes. No one watches, no one follows.
- No one stops anything.
- We changed the warehouse phone?
A day or two more,
and we are back to business.
We watch, we are careful.
But we are back to business.
We will have to do a favor
for our friend. Fair is fair.
The Colombians, I think.
They take our chemicals
and pay less than promised.
Down there,
I understand everyone is a terrorist now.
Judges are killed.
Bombs go off in the street. It's very bad.
The Colombians who cheated us
are not with the guerrillas.
They're trash.
The world is a smaller place now.
And the FBI cares very much
about such things.
Fair is fair, eh?
Sergei's making a call.
- Yes?
- Another box tomorrow, but clean.
Clean, yes.
If there is no problem,
bring in the la-z-boys. I will meet you.
- Recognize that voice?
- The man from the warehouse phone.
- That's the same guy?
- Same guy, new number.
Who you calling?
Pearlman, at home. Another affidavit
and we're back on the main stem.
Shit is raw, string. I mean,
you can stomp on this motherfucker.
All right. When them police
stop busting heads in them towers,
you let prop Joe's people
take the three of them.
All right.
Ok, add the dnr stuff
to the boilerplate, and you're there.
Connect the dots and you have to ask
yourself what these guys aren't into.
- Drugs, women, stolen goods.
- FBI didn't have much.
Something out of San Diego on glekas
in a stolen goods case.
San Diego? These guys move around.
- What's with the suit?
- Date night.
Undercover at the brothel.
Run like hell, ma'am.
We wanna be up on that phone
to hear what we hear after tonight's raid.
Who's the affiant?
Can you get the sl-series in pacific blue?
That would be best.
- Whatever you need, chief.
- I don't care about the color of this.
Ain't a problem.
They all just gotta have sunroofs.
- It's a long story.
- Next Tuesday would be good for us.
A ship comes Wednesday early, so...
Listen... you think I can get
an advance on this?
I got some expenses right now,
and I'm a little tapped.
- I'm just asking.
- Payment on delivery.
Don't worry about it. I would never
cheat a smart businessman like yourself.
It ain't enough that
I gotta think this whole shit through.
That I gotta be the one looking out
for this shit and that shit.
Checking up, making sure this shit
is done. No, that's not enough.
That's why they be paying
them fucking CEOs so much money.
Because when the shit fall bad,
it all fall bad on them.
Everybody else can be ducking and hiding,
doing what they fucking wanna do.
But when push come to shove, I'm the one
who's got to take that responsibility
and y'all are leaving me
very little to work with.
- Hold up, string...
- No, that's a simple thing, my nigger.
You drive the guns to the water.
You look around, you ain't see anybody,
you throw the guns... in the water.
Splash.
Now, get the fuck out of here, man.
Exceptyou, young'UN.
You ain't say shit?
No, they fucked up when they told me
my prints was on a gun.
I wiped them shits down myself.
And the one they said was mine wasn't even.
If they would've had anything past my name,
they would've kept me, right?
- All right.
- All right, string.
Lock that door.
You got a bolt cutter? I need a good one.
Got two in the window there.
You hung this on a duck?
Of course.
1,200.
Fair enough.
- Nick.
- It's been a while, Mikey.
Yeah, it has.
But your name's been in my mind lately.
Yeah?
My man called.
Said you was gonna take a re-up from me.
Yeah, that's what they told me, too.
Nicky sobotka, living the life.
Who fucking knew?
- How much you looking for?
- Two or three g-packs a week.
I was getting that from the Greek's people.
Four each.
Four? I wholesale for five, man.
I don't know. They told me you was
gonna be straight with it, so...
Sergei. What up, dawg?
I got a friend of yours here
says we're giving gs at four. Yeah?
All right, fuck it. Yeah, it's fine.
Another thing.
I wanna know it wasn't your people
dropped that body over on potee street.
I'm asking cause it was someone
with a Greek-ass name
and fucked if he
wasn't dumped by a house I was using.
Did he have hands? Did he have a face?
Yes? Then it wasn't us.
Idiot.
You got friends in high places, Nicky.
- Four a pack for you.
- All right, cool.
Thank god for
the Russian's cellphone.
They might be laying off the warehouse,
but he ain't changing.
Did he have hands?
Did he have a face?
Yes? Then it wasn't us.
- What the fuck is that?
- It's a man's purse.
European men like yourself
sometimes carry one.
Them people ain't right over there.
The mic has to go somewhere.
Besides, you might have hands
all over you before we get what we need.
Indeed I might, luv.
It'll be your call
when we come through the doors.
You want us in, you say... what was it?
"Spot on." It means "exactly".
Remember, they have to bring up
the money and sex first,
then an overt attempt to... engage.
Spot on.
Detective freamon with Baltimore homicide.
What do you guys have
in vicap for male victims,
headless or faceless,
and missing both hands?
- State?
- Middle Atlantic region.
Four and a half million in the capital
budget that's set to pass house and senate.
- Money'll be allocated for next year.
- Congratulations, frank.
What kind of stevedore drinks champagne?
So, nat, about the election.
I just need one more year
to bring the dredging home.
Ott's turn, frank.
Frank. This is agent koutris
of the FBI in Washington.
He's with the counterterrorism people
down there.
- Terrorism?
- He needs our help tonight.
Some enchanted evening
you will see a stranger
you will see a stranger...
11-34, what's your 20?
- I'm at the overpass on wicomico.
- Copy that.
Ok, we're on here.
Good evening.
Paint pigments. They ship them in
for the scl plant down at Fairfield.
It's in there somewhere. Run it.
Same consistencies on all the barrels.
- Nothing else in there.
- Nothing but the pigments.
- What's going on?
- I don't know nothing, horse.
Swear to god. Tonight I'm just
a dumb white boy from locust point.
I'm saying this out of respect, bri.
I love the man like my brother,
but for something like this,
he gonna listen to you more than me.
You think so?
All I put in his ear about my son
didn't do a damn thing, did it?
I told him that he needed to do more
for d'Angelo... and what happened?
He feel for that.
He feel for you.
I know he didn't see it coming.
- None of us seen it coming.
- I did.
I swear, I saw it.
He ain't listen to me then.
Why you think he gonna listen now?
Cause we got a weak product
and we holding on to prime real estate
with no muscle.
I don't got wee-bey, stinkum, bird.
I know that your heart is heavy.
I know.
But them wolves is at that door.
As long as them towers
are still standing, I am, too.
And I'll be damned if! Let
everything we fought for go to shit.
So I'll talk to him.
Mr. Cromwell.
Decisions, decisions.
Would it be wrong to take two?
Attaboy.
We should get upstairs.
Nothing but paint pigments.
Trust me, old friend. It's there.
Son of a bitch!
Ok, then.
Right. Er...
Maybe, we could, erm...
Talk about this first?
Yeah?
Hang on. Erm...
We, er...
- Any time you guys want.
- The money changed hands, right?
Sounded that way.
- And they talked about sex?
- Definitely.
Any time you guys want... hang on.
Oh, god.
- Jesus Christ.
- Is it soup yet?
- Spot something. Spot on it.
- Let's go.
- Whoa. Why?
- We're supposed to get in quick.
Calm the fuck down. They ain't gonna
flush a half-dozen whores down the toilet.
- Who is it?
- Baltimore police.
- What do you want?
- To lock your ass up.
Hands. Let me see 'em. Hands.
- Two more in the back.
- Come on, ladies.
You're late.
- He ok?
- He'll live.
Estimated at 1,125 kilograms
of processed crack cocaine
is estimated to be in
excess of $45 million.
Federal officials have confirmed
that their investigation is ongoing
and that while no arrests have been made,
the seizure itself has severely
disrupted the operations of a group
believed to have ties
to Colombian terrorist...
That, gentlemen, is a case.
God forbid you should put something
like that on my friend frank sobotka.
I would die happy.
- Our case is progressing.
- Great. What can you charge?
We're not at that point.
We've got wires into an operation
linked to drugs and women.
In all likelihood, the people
bringing in the girls
who were dead in that can two months ago.
We're on one location we believe is
a transshipment point for narcotics.
And last night, you'll see we hit a brothel
that we also think ties in.
A month or two more on the taps and dnrs
and we will identify the top-end players.
- You hit a brothel?
- Waterfront condo, high-end.
Jesus.
If you find anything that looks
like a list of steady customers, flush it.
Half the names in the Maryland manual
are probably on it.
Any problems on the raid?
A complication or two.
Nothing we can't write around.
Immigration is holding the girls.
The madam, who has legal residency,
we cut loose on bail.
- You try to interview them?
- Not while the taps are up.
Better to let them think it was random
and see what's said on the wire today.
Cut to the chase.
You any closer on my murders?
If these are the people who were importing
those girls, then we're closer.
The more we learn, the more
chance we have to clear those cases.
What about frank sobotka?
I'm not hearing his name in here anywhere.
The union may be involved in the smuggling,
but it doesn't go past that.
- This is about frank sobotka.
- The case is bigger now.
Look, missy, this is
my detail. I started it.
Now, I'm asking,
do you have charges on frank sobotka?
Charging sobotka now would lose us
a chance at the real targets.
- He is the real target.
- Patience, Stan.
- I'm sure if they bring the case...
- You owe me on this, erv.
You asked for a detail,
I gave you a detail.
You asked for Daniels, I gave you Daniels.
Ok. So, now the votes are in
and you're moving your golf trophies
upstairs to the commissioner's office,
now you're freezing me out, huh?
Fucking rat fuckers, all of you.
This is my case. Mine!
And now you're gonna tell me
who the target is?
Not fucking likely.
He's saying no. He's saying
we fought for every one of them towers
and to give them up now
would Mark us as weak.
He says if we do this,
prop Joe would have it over on us
and we might never get out from under.
We don't have the product or the muscle.
I told him. I did.
He say he still trying to find us
a better connect.
And for muscle... he's saying
he sending us the best he can find.
Brother mouzone.
He sending in brother?
From New York. Coming down to work
on retainer, for as long as we need.
- Brother mouzone?
- Yep.
"At which point
the officer was unable to resist
"the ministrations
of the aforementioned suspect
"and found himself
brought to the point of a sexual act."
You're famous behind this,
you know that?
As a pervert, this report is gonna make you
a bpd legend.
I can't perjure myself. I gotta explain it.
You have violated a half-dozen
departmental regs right there.
And no state's attorney
is gonna bring this into court.
The girls are being deported.
We did the raid just to tickle the wire.
There were two of them. I was outnumbered.
You fucking with me, right?
Brother mouzone, from NYC?
I told avon I didn't have enough muscle
to hold down them towers.
- And he reached out.
- Joe, I'm holding on to this deal.
- This is just shit we gotta deal with.
- Deal with how?
I would take the motherfucker out,
but avon can't know it came from me.
You don't think I'm gonna send any
of my people up against brother? Shit.
That nigger got more bodies on him
than a Chinese cemetery.
True.
Look, I'm just saying,
this your problem, not mine.
You want my product, you deal with it.
All right. We got some time here.
Avon gotta send the word
and wait for word to come back,
set up a price, talk to brother mouzone,
set up the whole shit.
That's a week or maybe two.
By then, your people's
gonna be in the towers
and if the money's right
then that is what it is.
Ain't no nigger from New York
gonna change the facts from the ground.
- 12-08 to 11-37, you there?
- 11-37, what you got?
That last truck is on the move. It sits there
for days and they don't off-load a thing.
- 10-4.
- They're testing us. Moving clean cans.
- The trash hasn't drawn any flies.
- No?
- We took out the last of it. No problems.
- Ok, then we go.
- What about ilona?
- She is home. They kept the children.
There are always more children.
Why don't we tap that cellphone, even
if we don't know who we're tapping?
That call mightjust be our PC.
And this here is the
little king of everything.
So how many we got in this sector?
Double shift, plus the flex squad, deu...
And a dozen guys tactical sent us.
We're on every corner.
Pretty damn quiet today.
Today.
Let's go.
Officer.