Him on the ball, from Dunbar.
He junior college now, but he going
to bigger places if he can make them grades.
He our edge, right there.
- Where he going?
- I don't know.
Uh, Terps, Hoyas, Missouri, Kansas,
they all want this cat.
So we in the mix too now.
You know what I'm talking about?
Proposition Joe
ain't got nobody balling like this.
He better not have one motherfucker like this.
I'm tired of losing to these Eastside bitches.
It's been three years running now, man.
Fucking with my morale, for real.
What happened to the faggot?
Omar?
- That nigger in the wind, man.
- What you mean he in the wind, man?
This city ain't that big.
You know what that nigger do
when he holed up somewhere?
He peel off one or two packages,
roll around the neighborhood
giving away free vials and shit.
On some real Robin Hood type shit.
If we try and get at him,
we gonna have two dozen niggers
saying that we on our way.
If you want us to hunt that nigger,
we gonna hunt.
But the smart play, I think, we call a truce,
put this thing on hold for a hot second,
let the faggot get comfortable,
and when he do, he'll pop up his head -
boom, we got him.
What motherfuckers gonna be saying
while we waiting? Hmm?
What people gonna say when they see
this cocksucking faggot out in the sunshine?
Like it ain't no thing to take my shit.
- Kid's everything I said he was, huh?
- Yeah, he's straight.
Don't know what we're gonna do
without him.
- How come you ain't signed?
- Lot of schools looking at me.
- I'm listening.
- Ten large, though, that ain't bad.
- It ain't.
- Well, ten for the kid, plus five.
Uh, donation for the program.
Done.
Good. Give me 30 from the line
and get out of here.
- Yo, man, good job, baby.
- All right.
And I assume there's another five right here,
for making this happen?
Ain't shit for free, right?
If you walk through the garden
You'd better watch your back
But I beg your pardon
Walk the straight and narrow track
If you walk with Jesus
He'll save your soul
You gotta keep the devil
Down in the hole
All the angels sing
About Jesus' mighty sword
And they shield you with their wings
Keep you close to the Lord
Don't pay heed to temptation
For his hands are so cold
You gotta keep the devil
Way down in the hole
So, what you do for money?
Can't live without it, right?
You still fucked up
behind that stick-up, man?
Shit ain't on you. It ain't on me neither.
Motherfucker who robbed
the stash shot Sterling.
He gonna get got
no matter what you or me do.
I just don't wanna play.
I don't wanna play no more. All right?
I was thinking about going to school,
over at Edmondson,
ask if they'll let me back in.
- What grade?
- Ninth.
- Ninth? Shit, you how old?
- 16.
Damn, man, you supposed
to be a junior by now.
I heard Stinkum got killed.
Yeah.
Damn.
- Yo, I said I don't wanna play.
- I heard you.
And you ain't got to do nothing.
I heard you. Take it.
Hurry up, nigger. People looking.
Look here, man,
you a smart little motherfucker.
You start back up at Edmondson,
you likely to finish up at Harvard
or some shit like that. Believe, B.
And you - you got a good heart in there too.
Not like the rest of these niggers.
- Yeah?
- 'Ronnie Mo on Tower Phone 2.'
Right.
'Yo, you coming to get this shit?'
'Keep cool. We making rounds.'
- 'You know I ain't moving like I used to.'
- 'Couple of hours, we be at you.'
'All right.'
Wee-Bey picking up at the towers?
- In a couple hours, give or take.
- Time enough for us to make a play.
- What's up with Wallace?
- Nothing.
- Nothing?
It's all good, just leave him be.
Damn.
Fuck.
I'm tired of not having
a phone up in this joint.
- I'll be right back.
- Yeah.
- Have a nice hike.
- You make order?
- Who this?
You make order? Good yakame.
- 'What?'
- Or no delivery.
You make order, you come get.
Good yakame, good noodle.
Extra ketchup.
What the fuck was that?
That was my Korean counterman.
Sounded Chinese.
Like you can fucking tell the difference.
It's a brave new world for you, boys.
- 12-14.
- '12-14.'
- Request a lateral with 12-08.
- 'Go ahead, 14.'
- 08, can you go to Channel 3?
- 12-08, I got that.
- 'Where you at?'
- McCullough above Preston.
On a good pay phone
that the Pit boys are now using.
'I'm up on the church. Hang close, boys.
'Might have a nice jack-up for you two.'
I can't believe you boys still in business.
- Testers coming in five.
- What's the new package, man?
Yellow tops. This shit is the bomb.
- Shit is the bomb.
- Check it.
A man who wants to get high more than clean.
- He was doing good, too.
- That shit was bullshit.
- Them meetings were just fronts.
- The man sounded strong.
Whatever.
It's about that time.
- Shit.
- What happened?
That's the boy who beat me down, man.
Hey, yo. The shits right here
is yellow tops and they right,
so remember where you caught this blast
and tell your fiend-ass friends.
Line the fuck up.
Back up.
Get in line, what the fuck? Line the fuck up.
Get the fuck out of here. Fuck y'all.
There you go!
Hurry up. Over here.
Get one, girl, over here. I got one, I got one.
- You get one?
- I got one.
Yo, hold up. Hey. Hey. You catch one?
You know, I got three if you need.
You was at the meeting
over at Samuel Morse.
- Mr. One-Day Man. It wasn't even that.
- Stood up, though.
Why you at the tester line
if you ain't chasing?
Trying to get my nephew off the corner.
His mama sent him up to Cumberland.
Try to keep him clean at my grandma's.
He ain't anywhere near his bottom.
Got to see that bottom coming up at him.
Hard too, cos he's young, 24.
Most people don't get tired till they're 35, 40.
- How old are you?
- Young at heart.
Waylon, man.
Bubs.
Give them a long rope. The farther away
from the projects, the less risk to the wire.
- Hell with the wire.
- Excuse me?
'Gotcha, McNulty, you're too easy.'
You can come at this a few ways.
First thing is we need the names
of all front companies,
limited partnerships, LLCs, and all that mess.
- LLCs?
- Limited liability corporations.
Start with the nightclub Barksdale owns.
Look up Orlando's, by address, you match it,
and you see it's owned by who?
It's on Baltimore Street, right?
Got it. D & B enterprises.
Hand it over to Prez
who's gonna get off his ass
and walk over to
the state office buildings on Preston Street.
- Preston Street?
- Corporate charter office.
Corporate who?
'They have the paperwork
on every corporation and LLC
'licensed to do business in the state.
'Look up D & B Enterprises on the computer.
You're going to get a little reel of microfilm.
'Pull the corporate charter papers that way.
Write down every name you see.
'Corporate officers, shareholders
or, more importantly,
'the resident agent on the filing
who is usually a lawyer.
'While they use front names
as corporate officers,
'they usually use the same lawyer
to do the charter filing.
'Find that agent's name,
run it through the computer,
'find out what other corporations
he's done the filing for,
'and that way we find other front companies.'
While he's doing that, what do I do?
Keep your head in this assessment book.
Look up any properties
that you can connect to Barksdale.
How do you know it connects to Barksdale?
'You work off what Prez gets you
from the corporate charter documents.
'Whatever companies he links to Barksdale
or people connected to him,
'look for those companies
in the city land records.'
- Huh?
- For example,
McNulty said
that he heard that Barksdale owned
an apartment building up on Druid Park Lake.
'Look up all the blocks on Reservoir Hill.
'See if there's anything
owned by D & B Enterprises
'or any other company that Prez finds
through corporate charter or anything similar.
'If you find something that fits,
you write down the folio number,
'so you can look it up later at the courthouse.
'You don't find anything,
'take the names of all the corporate listings
for the multi-units near the lake.
'You call that list over to Prez,
who pulls the charter papers,
'and he'll look for connections.'
- This is like a scavenger hunt.
- But what if Barksdale is careful?
What if we can't find his name on anything?
In this country, somebody's name
has got to be on a piece of paper.
A cousin, a girlfriend,
a grandmother, a lieutenant he can trust.
Somebody's name is on a piece of paper.
And here's the rub.
You follow drugs,
you get drug addicts and drug dealers.
But you start to follow the money
and you don't know where
the fuck it's gonna take you.
While we're running around on this,
what are you gonna do?
- You need something?
- Yeah.
Let me get the campaign financial reports
for the western districts
and, actually, any citywide race.
Quarterly reports or individual donor lists?
- Both, please.
- It'll be a couple of hundred pages.
Really? I'll take all of it.
What the fuck, man?
With your right hand,
reach for the window and open the door.
- Hurry up, man.
- Step out of the car.
Drop the cane, toss the cane.
Come around to the back.
Turn around.
Sir, is there anything in the vehicle
we should know about?
Nope.
No guns, drugs?
Me ain't got shit.
This money right here,
I didn't just pull this out of your truck?
What money?
- We'll be counting this limp-dick cash all day.
- Where you guys going with this?
Like the man said, it ain't ours.
It ain't yours? So, you don't mind
if we just take it off your hands?
Do what you feel.
You pretending to take money.
- I didn't even know it was there.
- I know how that shit is.
The other day,
I took up the sofa cushions off my couch
and found $1.40 I didn't even know was there.
You all ain't got no charge, right?
No, fucker, we do not have a charge.
We just got your money.
You want it back, you can explain it
to the state's attorney where you got it.
Y'all enjoy your day now, you hear?
As I wake up in the morning
and get out of my bed
- I'm thinkin' 'bout the brothers...
- Give me three.
The brothers I deal with, locked up
As I wake up in the morning
and get out of my bed
I'm thinkin' 'bout the people I grew up with,
long dead
The brothers I grew up with, locked up
I'm freestylin' off the top of my head
You know it's swell, Patti LaBelle
I like her but Regina Belle is better...
Motherfucker!
Yo, motherfucker, trying to steal our shit.
Fished your wish, Bubs?
Oh, yeah.
And you should've seen
the one that got away.
You know, I nearly got killed
behind this caper.
It's all in the game, Bubs.
Yeah?
Yo, Bub...
This ain't shit.
I'm not high, neither.
It's fucking Arm & Hammer.
We just been firing baking soda.
Fuck. It's all right.
I'll just come up with another plan.
- I did it once, right?
- Shh.
Fuck me.
Carv, you go to a restaurant,
and say the waitress gives you
good, decent service.
- How much do you tip?
- How much do I tip?
- For good service.
- I don't know, 15%.
- Some people tip 20.
- Some people got money.
How much you think Wee-Bey would tip?
You'd be a clever motherfucker
if there wasn't a wiretap running.
What do you mean?
Say we turn in 20, and this afternoon
the bosses are listening to the wiretap
and they hear we took 30 out of that car.
Didn't think of that, did you?
We're finding stuff
on the west side of downtown
that might be his
over by that Howard Street corridor.
- What kind of property?
- Low-rent commercials. A lot of vacants.
What does Avon Barksdale want
with a string of empty storefronts?
- This feels premature.
- What does?
Chasing up assets. We're not close
to putting a charge to the man.
- That should be the priority.
- We put a charge to him,
the deputy shuts us down,
tells us to go home.
You want the money side of this case,
it's now or never.
Whoop-whoop!
- I'm working here.
- Whoop-whoop!
- Maybe 20 or 30.
- Dollars for donuts.
You should've seen the looks on their faces.
- What did Wee-Bey say?
- "What money?"
The only hassle is we need to count this shit.
- Do the ECU Submissions.
- It's all limp-dick, dime-vial money.
Dirty bills right off the corner.
You all got the Pit boys on a fresh payphone?
- On McCullough.
- You take pictures?
We're gonna need an additional affidavit
to get up on that phone.
Another 30 days, McNulty?
What the fuck did I do?
One day he fights, next he's ready to roll over.
- Does he want this fucking case or not?
- Give him some slack.
He's wrestling with the angels on this one.
Where's my lucky pen?
'You ready, bitch?'
'I'm ready.
'I wanna get on my knees
and suck you like a big lollipop.'
- 'Suck it.'
- 'I know that's your favorite.'
'Let me lick that. You like that?'
'I want you to butt-fuck me...'
We're supposed to turn off the tap
when it's non-pertinent.
Fuck, no, this is too good.
- 'Fuck me.'
- 'Ooh, Daddy, yeah. Oh! Oh!'
There's no way I'm transcribing this stuff.
'Touch yourself.
- 'Oh, yeah. My pussy is so wet right now.'
- Phone sex?
Shit was hilarious.
You're supposed to shut down
if it's non-pertinent.
- 'You're gonna look like a glazed donut.'
- 'Is that right?'
'I'm gonna get there and fuck you
in all three holes.'
- 'You're gonna come past?'
- 'Tomorrow, yeah.
'But I need to go past Argyle Street tonight,
check in with Wallace.
'He off the hook since we helped
the tower crew get that stick-up boy.
'Wallace is bugging. Don't hardly even
come out of that room no more.'
- 'Why he be like that?'
- 'I think he might be getting high.'
- 'Boy is scaring me.'
- 'You holler at me later.'
'That'll work.'
Pertinent now, right?
It is if you can explain why we're on the line
after 10 minutes jerking off.
You gotta justify that.
Maybe three holes was the code
for three stash houses.
Omar!
Yo!
Omar coming, Omar coming!
- Did you hear me? Omar coming.
- Let's get out of here.
Close that shit down
I said, Omar coming through.
Somebody in trouble now. Let's go.
Eyy-yo.
Y'all need to open this door, man,
before I huff and puff.
By the hairs of your chinny-chin-chin.
You best roll out.
We up in here with a MAC-10.
I thinks not, Terrell, I thinks not.
Y'all might need to think this through
and stop wasting my time.
Because Omar can come back tomorrow.
And the next day.
And I will put a bullet in all y'all behind,
what happen right now, you heard?
Fair enough.
Here you go, keep it.
How do you wanna play it?
Hard and tight, like she's got no choice.
- Shardene Ennis.
- Miss, we need to talk.
- About what?
- It's a downtown talk.
This way. Come on. Come on.
Two at a time! Two at a time!
Give me a two and two.
- Yo, what's up?
- What you got?
Family affair, two-for-one, you up?
- Nah, not me.
- All right.
How you figure all these little pebbles
get up on top of the roof?
Where's everybody at?
Maybe the whole thing is over
and no one bothered to tell us.
Maybe we won.
Something ain't right.
Come on, let's take a ride.
I like these.
Yeah?
- The toy furniture is great.
- Doll house miniatures.
It's a hobby.
My sister had a doll house when we were
young, but nothing as nice as these. Can I?
Sure, babe.
That's a walnut marble-top vanity.
Renaissance revival, late 19th century.
Do you have a house for them?
No, I just make them and sell them.
That seems kind of sad.
You should have a house for them.
We can use the Lieutenant's office.
- No.
- I ain't asked for nothing.
Oh. What's up, Tasha?
You got too pretty, girl.
Go inside, Tash.
I'm thinking, um...
Thinking about getting clean... again.
I was thinking I ain't got
no other place to go, maybe...
That's wrong, right?
That ain't right, right? Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Wait.
Back door only.
There's an old sofa in the basement.
I'll throw you down some blankets.
You try to come up those stairs,
and I'm gonna call the police. I swear I will.
West fucking Baltimore is on vacation.
No crews slinging in the
low-rises, the towers.
What the fuck?
- Who's playing who?
- West against East.
- Baltimore?
- The projects, man.
The bragging rights to the projects.
The projects got a ball team?
How long you been working at Orlando's?
- Four or five months.
- You like it?
- Pays the rent.
- You must see a lot there, I imagine.
- What do you mean?
- There's a lot of game being played.
I just work for tips.
- For tips?
- Tips, drinks.
I'm just a b-girl.
I don't mess with nothing beyond that.
Some of the girls in there, they're into drugs.
Some of them turn tricks in the rooms
upstairs but I mostly just stay at the bar.
Hmm.
It's rare when we ask somebody
to come downtown with us, with no charge,
we don't tell them what we're gonna talk
about, and they come without complaining.
- That hardly ever happens.
- Rarely, if ever.
- I figure you got your reasons.
- The crew that runs Orlando's.
They've dropped about a dozen bodies
over the last year.
They're running the drugs in every housing
project west of the Martin Luther King.
I don't know anything about that.
I just work for tips.
Now you do know, because we're telling you.
You know a girl named Keisha Michaels?
- She dances with me.
- How's she doing?
All right, I guess.
Will you excuse us a moment?
- So, what do you think?
- I think she's a sweetheart.
If we push her hard, she'll tumble.
You want to show her the pictures?
I want to do better than that.
Come on, man, play defense.
- Let's go!
- D-up, B.
- Who is he?
- That's Marcus Rivera, man.
He out of Lake Clifton.
That nigger played in Italy and shit.
Yo, Slim. What's up, man? You got to go
all the way to Europe to get you a ringer?
He home now. But I see you
pulling boys out the junior colleges.
He from Eastside, went to Dunbar.
Playboy, how come you wearing that suit?
It's 85 fucking degrees
and you trying to be like Pat Riley.
Look the part, be the part, motherfucker.
You got a fake fucking clipboard.
You can't even read a playbook.
Be for real. Bunch of bitches.
Yeah!
- Let's go.
- That was nice.
That boy was talking to God, right?
Oh!
Ain't y'all on the clock?
- Ain't you?
- We on a break.
Then we on a break too.
What's up with this game?
Just something we do every year.
Eastside versus Westside niggers.
Loser gotta throw a big-ass party
at Druid Hill next week.
- Who's favored?
- Eastside won the last two years.
My boys.
Found nude Monday morning,
in a dumpster off Reisterstown Road.
Toxicology is positive for heroin and cocaine.
- In a dumpster?
- Rolled up in a rug.
She overdosed and whoever was with her
just rolled her up and threw her away.
That's how they do.
Positive for semen in vaginal,
anal and oral cavities.
- Three different blood types, all secretors.
- They fucked her and threw her away.
The only reason we knew who she was
or what she was about
or what she might mean to someone like you
is because we've been keeping an eye
on the people who run Orlando's.
We got ways of knowing
what they're saying, thinking.
- You know what they said about this one?
- Bitch didn't know how good the snort was.
That it was her own fault. That's how they do.
They use people, and when they throw them
away, they find a way to say it ain't on them.
Lying motherfucker.
He said they took her to a hospital.
- Now get back on D.
- Check out Avon. He's freaking.
Shit, man, we got to win this one.
Yo, I think Avon's here.
- Where?
- Like I know what he looks like.
He's a black guy rooting for Westside.
We might have a visual on Avon.
Street ball game up at Cloverdale.
- Where's Greggs and Freamon?
- Pressing the stripper they picked up.
You and Carver stay on the radio.
- We should follow him.
- Why?
He ain't gonna touch drugs or money
anywhere you can see him, Lieutenant.
In Narcotics we follow guys.
We do it well, we make cases on it.
Mount up.
We been on this guy three months.
Don't you even wanna get a look at him?
I wouldn't know Avon Barksdale
if I fell over him in the street.
I don't need to. We get him by voice alone
or we don't get him.
Yeah, baby!
Half-time.
You got yourself a fine ringer.
Yeah, baby, it's not your year.
- It look that way, but you never know.
- I know, man, we up 12.
You is, but I got a proposition for you.
- Okay.
- Double down?
Let's give this wager a clean six figures.
You serious? I don't give a fuck.
It's your money. You can waste it if you want.
- Anyone got him?
- '64-Charlie to central K.'
12-10.
'12-10.'
You have him?
Lieutenant, I don't even know
what I'm looking for.
Yeah, that's what I'm talkin' about.
Got him marked. On the sideline, red shirt,
white visor. I think he's coaching.
Yo, who this fucking midget, yo?
Get that midget out of here, B.
Hey.
'Why you holler at me?'
'We getting down to it.'
- 'I get to you when I get to you.'
- That's it, we're on the stash.
- We are?
- Mmm-hmm.
How can you put that down
when Sydnor wasn't on the roof?
Yes, he was.
No, he's not, he's with Daniels.
No, he isn't.
Oooh!
- Get the fuck out of here.
- Ref, what the fuck?
What the fuck?
Ref! Ref, what the fuck?
The boy was fouled. Clear, straight up!
How you gonna not call that?
I can put time back on the clock and replay it.
You talking about a do-over?
A fucking do-over?
That's not how the game is played!
You can't do that!
Nigger talking about doing it again.
- I don't want any trouble.
- Ain't gonna be no trouble over no ball.
Man, you supposed to be the ref.
Why don't you stand up
for your fucking self? You pussy.
You can't let any old motherfucking nigger
get in your face, understand?
Walk away. Walk away!
Turn around and walk the fuck away.
Ignorant motherfucker.
- We cool?
- We cool, baby.
Tell your people to come to the park
Saturday at noon.
You come on the Westside again,
without a ball, I'm gonna light your ass up.
- D'Angelo, huh?
- You know him?
At this point, it feels like I do.
We sort of moved in together.
He seemed like he was different.
- I have to quit the club.
- Yes, you do. But not just yet.
We need your help.
Which is why we came to you.
- I don't know what else...
- Keisha was not the first.
Unless somebody steps up a little bit,
she's not gonna be the last neither.
You like that one?
Why don't you keep it?
Thank you.
- He's getting into a black Ford Excursion.
- 'Copy that.'
He's pulling out, north on Collington.
'11-71.'
You got the parallel on the north,
I got him on the south.
11-71, I got him.
Looks like he's going east on Oliver.
Some make a livin' doin' killin'...
Pass the information or pass the wine
Pass the buck or pass the baton
But you can't pass
the police or the Pentagon...
He just parked. East of Oliver.
12-10, you keep the eyeball.
11-71, take up a position on Federal,
west of Montford.
I'm coming up from the south.
11-71, I copy that.
He's just sitting there.
...television and radio stations...
- He's doubling back.
- 'Copy.'
He's south on Montford.
He jumped the light at Preston and Milton
and is south on Milton.
Be advised that he didn't make it to Chase.
11-71, what's your status?
'He couldn't have gone past us.'
'11-71, nothing on this side.'
'Must have went to ground.'
Hold your positions. I'll take a look.
...fuck the constitution
Are we part of the solution
or are we part of the pollution?
Sittin' by and wonderin' why
Things ain't the way we like to find them to be
To be, for you and for me, the people
over there and the ones in between...
- He called again, same payphone.
- Same voice?
Main stash house, it's got to be.
The pattern fits.
- Who took the call at the projects?
- Who knows?
There was no one on the roof. Sydnor was
off with Daniels, chasing Avon in the street.
We had a good day too. Kima turned
one of the dancers over at Avon's club.
The one who's fucking D'Angelo.
This guy's good.
We threw everything we had at him.
You know what they say,
stupid criminals make stupid cops.
I'm proud to be chasing this guy.
We got four front companies so far,
buying up all kinds of shit.
A club, an apartment building, a funeral home
and real estate on the west side
of downtown by the Howard Street corridor.
Shop fronts and warehouses.
- Barksdale's name on it?
- Fronts, mostly. Relatives, some.
Mind if I have a seat?
He's had the projects for more than a year
and it's a money factory.
We popped Wee-Bey coming out
the other day with 22,000.
The boys on the wire were saying
it wasn't much of a loss.
22?
One morning from the towers and the Pit.
Add the avenue corners, you're up near 30.
Another take for the evening, 60,000.
- A day?
- That's 25 million a year, conservatively.
Take out 20%
for running expenses and spillage
and you are still clearing
a million dollars a month.
- So, where does it all go?
- He shows no flash.
He's got no, uh, no house, no car in his name,
no jewelry, no clothes.
Just front companies and the property.
And political contributions.
75,000 last month alone, all from
his front companies or their listed officers.
And that's just at a quick glance.
I'm just totaling up the legal contributions.
You've got the likes of Damien Price,
aide to a state senator,
driving out 20,000 in cash from the projects
whenever he feels it.
I know you don't wanna hear this,
but the money is real and it's everywhere.
And more than the drugs,
it's the money that matters.
I ain't fucked nobody else
if that's what you thinking.
All right. I mean, fuck it.
If you wanna go, then go!
But you could give me a goddamn reason.
- What do I look like to you?
- What you mean?
- You look like a girl, a woman.
A beautiful woman. You fine. What?
I don't look like trash to you?
Baby, this ain't about what you do.
I don't look like something you could
roll up in a rug and throw in the trash?
Shardene.
Shardene!
Lieutenant, you paged us?
We were almost home.
Sit.
'Hey, checked my count again.'
'How bad?'
'Not too bad, man.
- 'We got hit about 22.'
- '22? That's all?
'All right.'
I got towers two, three, five and six
and another one labelled "P" for the Pit.
Where's one and four? It's on the wire
that we took them for 22.
You shitheads turned in 15. Where's the rest?
Lieutenant, we ain't got...
You have till roll call tomorrow to crawl back
to whatever rock you hid it under.
It comes back and it goes to ECU.
This doesn't happen.
Not with me. Not with my unit.
I wouldn't steal and not tell you about it.
This some of Avon's shit.
You got Avon Barksdale chasing
your ass all around town
and you still find time to take his shit.
- It's your shit now.
- What I want with that?
What anybody want with that, man?
- How much you asking?
- We free.
Free?
I'm saying, I got a little proposition for you.
Proposition is, you get four G-packs for free,
you give me some better idea
on how I can reach Avon.
- How to contact him?
- You all just had a game, right?
How you get a hold of him to parley?
We talk now and then.
I page his ass.
Okay. Okay.
- That all you need? A number?
- I could make do with it.
And a code for one of his peoples.
What Wee-Bey use, 07?
07.
What makes you think I ain't gonna take this
and throw your ass up outta here?
Avon goes down, the projects
be open market again, right?
Let me understand.
Avon loses 100 large to me on a bet,
then you bring me some of his shit so that
I can put your predatory self on his ass.
Not his day, is it?
Fuck it.
Fuck. Fuck.
Ah!
Fuck it.
- Where was it?
- The wheel well.
You remember when the bag broke?
Think Daniels will believe it?
Would you?
You didn't believe me.
I'm sorry.
Savino late. I'm ready to make
this money-run, get the fuck out here.
- You tired?
- I'm tired, man, I'm hungry.
Me, too. Want something to eat
from the diner?
You going over there?
Get me a cheese steak.
- You hungry too?
- I could do a burger.
Let me get onions on that, man.
You organizing it right? My 50s with my 50s,
and my 100s with my 100s?
All right, ladies, good night.
I see you all tomorrow, on time, you hear?
Count this money, baby.
- What the fuck?
- Who's that?
Wee-Bey swinging me an emergency call.
Fuck.
Bey?
Yeah.
911 call.
No, no, no, no.
We got rules, right?
Fuck.
Hey.
They had cheese fries, baby. I got you some.
Avon, stay down, man.
I got you covered.